tokens,labels
date: 2020-11-19,O
nol,O
##te,O
:,O
top,O
poll,O
##ster,O
finds,O
47,O
%,O
say,O
‘,O
likely,O
‘,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##ts,O
stol,O
##e,O
election,O
via,O
@,O
bre,ORG_B
##it,ORG_I
##bar,ORG_I
##tn,ORG_I
##ew,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
!,O
#,O
vote,O
#,O
mag,ORG_B
##a,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
“,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
told,O
us,O
for,O
some,O
time,O
we,O
would,O
be,O
getting,O
a,O
vaccine,O
by,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
the,O
year,O
and,O
people,O
lau,O
##ghe,O
##d,O
at,O
him,O
",",O
and,O
here,O
we,O
are,O
with,O
pfizer,ORG_B
getting,O
fda,ORG_B
approval,O
by,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
this,O
month,O
.,O
he,O
was,O
right,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
maria,PER_B
##bar,PER_I
##ti,PER_I
##rom,PER_I
##o,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
lawyer,O
##s,O
now,O
on,O
@,O
news,ORG_B
##max,ORG_I
",",O
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
&,O
amp,ORG_B
;,O
maybe,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
.,O
an,O
open,O
and,O
shut,O
case,O
of,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
.,O
massive,O
numbers,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
the,O
cov,O
##id,O
drugs,O
now,O
available,O
to,O
make,O
people,O
better,O
are,O
amazing,O
",",O
but,O
sel,O
##dom,O
talked,O
about,O
by,O
the,O
media,O
!,O
mortality,O
rate,O
is,O
85,O
%,O
down,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
in,O
detroit,O
is,O
ramp,O
##ant,O
",",O
and,O
has,O
been,O
for,O
many,O
years,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
“,O
only,O
because,O
of,O
president,O
trump,O
",",O
we,O
are,O
going,O
to,O
have,O
a,O
vaccine,O
by,O
the,O
end,O
of,O
the,O
year,O
.,O
”,O
ron,PER_B
##ny,PER_I
jackson,PER_I
",",O
texas,O
congress,O
##man,O
-,O
elect,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
we,O
are,O
making,O
big,O
progress,O
.,O
results,O
start,O
to,O
come,O
in,O
next,O
week,O
.,O
make,O
america,LOC_B
great,O
again,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
“,O
evidence,O
of,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
continues,O
to,O
grow,O
",",O
including,O
20,O
",",O
000,O
dead,O
people,O
on,O
the,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
vote,O
##rs,O
roll,O
and,O
many,O
thousands,O
all,O
over,O
the,O
country,O
.,O
now,O
",",O
there,O
has,O
been,O
an,O
artificial,O
number,O
of,O
votes,O
in,O
favor,O
of,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
.,O
”,O
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
almost,O
zero,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
rejected,O
in,O
georgia,ORG_B
this,O
election,O
.,O
in,O
years,O
past,O
",",O
close,O
to,O
4,O
%,O
.,O
not,O
possible,O
.,O
must,O
have,O
signature,O
check,O
on,O
envelope,O
##s,O
now,O
.,O
very,O
easy,O
to,O
do,O
.,O
dem,O
##s,O
fighting,O
because,O
they,O
got,O
caught,O
.,O
far,O
more,O
votes,O
than,O
needed,O
for,O
flip,O
.,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_I
must,O
get,O
tough,O
!,O
@,O
brian,PER_B
##ke,PER_I
##mp,PER_I
##ga,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
just,O
saw,O
the,O
vote,O
tabula,O
##tions,O
.,O
there,O
is,O
no,O
way,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
got,O
80,O
",",O
000,O
",",O
000,O
votes,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
this,O
was,O
a,O
100,O
%,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
we,O
will,O
win,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
happy,O
thanksgiving,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
watch,O
for,O
massive,O
ball,O
##ot,O
counting,O
abuse,O
and,O
",",O
just,O
like,O
the,O
early,O
vaccine,O
",",O
remember,O
i,O
told,O
you,O
so,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
no,O
thanks,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
ball,O
##ot,O
counting,O
abuse,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
great,O
book,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
a,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
a,O
total,O
fraud,O
.,O
state,O
##house,O
republic,O
##ans,O
",",O
proud,O
",",O
strong,O
and,O
honest,O
",",O
will,O
never,O
let,O
this,O
tra,O
##vest,O
##y,O
stand,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
highly,O
respected,O
ken,O
star,O
##r,O
:,O
“,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
’,O
s,O
three,O
-,O
day,O
extension,O
of,O
the,O
mail,O
-,O
in,O
ball,O
##ot,O
deadline,O
is,O
a,O
constitution,O
##al,O
tra,O
##vest,O
##y,O
.,O
”,O
legal,O
schola,O
##rs,O
agree,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
will,O
use,O
these,O
charts,O
in,O
court,O
case,O
.,O
the,O
election,O
was,O
a,O
ho,O
##ax,O
.,O
thank,O
you,O
justin,PER_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
will,O
go,O
down,O
much,O
further,O
.,O
weekend,O
day,O
##time,O
even,O
worse,O
",",O
dead,O
.,O
they,O
still,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
get,O
it,O
.,O
fantastic,O
alternatives,O
!,O
the,O
late,O
/,O
great,O
roger,PER_B
ai,PER_I
##les,PER_I
is,O
seriously,O
missed,O
",",O
but,O
i,O
still,O
won,O
legal,O
votes,O
by,O
a,O
lot,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
republic,O
##ans,O
",",O
don,O
’,O
t,O
let,O
andrew,PER_B
mcca,PER_I
##be,PER_I
continue,O
to,O
get,O
away,O
with,O
totally,O
criminal,O
activity,O
.,O
what,O
he,O
did,O
should,O
never,O
be,O
allowed,O
to,O
happen,O
to,O
our,O
country,O
again,O
.,O
fight,O
for,O
justice,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
@,O
justin,PER_B
_,O
hart,O
there,O
will,O
be,O
no,O
lock,O
##downs,O
other,O
than,O
those,O
done,O
by,O
certain,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##t,O
governors,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
so,O
much,O
truth,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
happy,O
245,O
##th,O
birth,O
##day,O
to,O
the,O
@,O
us,ORG_B
##mc,ORG_I
!,O
#,O
happy,O
##bi,O
##rth,O
##day,O
##mari,ORG_B
##nes,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
nat,PER_B
##e,PER_I
sim,PER_I
##ington,PER_I
",",O
a,O
very,O
smart,O
and,O
qualified,O
individual,O
",",O
is,O
having,O
his,O
senate,O
hearing,O
today,O
.,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_I
will,O
hopefully,O
confirm,O
him,O
to,O
the,O
fcc,ORG_B
asa,O
##p,O
!,O
we,O
need,O
action,O
now,O
on,O
this,O
very,O
important,O
nom,O
##ination,O
!,O
!,O
@,O
sen,O
##ator,O
##wick,PER_B
##er,PER_I
@,O
marsh,PER_B
##abl,PER_I
##ack,PER_I
##burn,PER_I
@,O
senate,O
##ma,O
##j,O
##ld,O
##r,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
party,O
leadership,O
votes,O
are,O
this,O
week,O
.,O
i,O
hope,O
they,O
pick,O
very,O
tough,O
and,O
smart,O
fight,O
##ers,O
.,O
we,O
will,O
win,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
rin,O
##o,O
mit,O
##t,O
rom,O
##ney,O
should,O
read,O
this,O
.,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
sure,O
",",O
however,O
",",O
that,O
he,O
feels,O
he,O
got,O
sla,O
##ught,O
##ering,O
by,O
obama,O
“,O
fair,O
and,O
square,O
”,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-26,O
a,O
bri,O
##lli,O
##ant,O
wo,O
##man,O
of,O
cour,O
##age,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
nat,PER_B
##e,PER_I
sim,PER_I
##ington,PER_I
",",O
a,O
very,O
smart,O
and,O
qualified,O
individual,O
",",O
is,O
having,O
his,O
senate,O
hearing,O
today,O
.,O
republic,O
##ans,O
will,O
hopefully,O
confirm,O
him,O
to,O
the,O
fcc,ORG_B
asa,O
##p,O
!,O
we,O
need,O
action,O
now,O
on,O
this,O
very,O
important,O
nom,O
##ination,O
!,O
!,O
@,O
sen,O
##ator,O
##wick,PER_B
##er,PER_I
@,O
marsh,PER_B
##abl,PER_I
##ack,PER_I
##burn,PER_I
@,O
senate,O
##ma,O
##j,O
##ld,O
##r,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
the,O
great,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
day,O
##time,O
ratings,O
cra,O
##sh,O
will,O
only,O
get,O
worse,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
ball,O
##ot,O
corruption,O
will,O
be,O
exposed,O
ton,O
##ight,O
at,O
9,O
:,O
00,O
##pm,O
##e,O
on,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
on,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
a,O
must,O
read,O
.,O
impossible,O
for,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
to,O
have,O
overcome,O
these,O
",",O
and,O
even,O
greater,O
",",O
odds,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
so,O
true,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
thank,O
you,O
elizabeth,PER_B
",",O
love,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
i,O
gave,O
a,O
long,O
news,O
conference,O
today,O
after,O
wishing,O
the,O
military,O
a,O
happy,O
thanksgiving,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
realized,O
once,O
again,O
that,O
the,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
media,O
coordinate,O
##s,O
so,O
that,O
the,O
real,O
message,O
of,O
such,O
a,O
conference,O
never,O
gets,O
out,O
.,O
primary,O
point,O
made,O
was,O
that,O
the,O
2020,O
election,O
was,O
rig,O
##ged,O
",",O
and,O
that,O
i,O
won,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
twitter,ORG_B
is,O
sending,O
out,O
totally,O
false,O
“,O
trends,O
”,O
that,O
have,O
absolutely,O
nothing,O
to,O
do,O
with,O
what,O
is,O
really,O
trending,O
in,O
the,O
world,O
.,O
they,O
make,O
it,O
up,O
",",O
and,O
only,O
negative,O
“,O
stuff,O
”,O
.,O
same,O
thing,O
will,O
happen,O
to,O
twitter,ORG_B
as,O
is,O
happening,O
to,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
day,O
##time,O
.,O
also,O
",",O
big,O
conservative,O
discrimination,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
thank,O
you,O
pens,LOC_B
##aco,LOC_I
##la,LOC_I
",",LOC_I
florida,LOC_I
!,O
together,O
",",O
we,O
are,O
going,O
to,O
make,O
america,LOC_B
great,O
again,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
we,O
have,O
great,O
support,O
on,O
the,O
election,O
ho,O
##ax,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
for,O
purposes,O
of,O
national,O
security,O
",",O
section,O
230,O
must,O
be,O
immediately,O
terminated,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
“,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
care,O
what,O
state,O
your,O
in,O
",",O
this,O
computer,O
voting,O
system,O
is,O
wide,O
open,O
to,O
fraud,O
and,O
intervention,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
lou,PER_B
##do,PER_I
##bb,PER_I
##s,PER_I
true,O
",",O
and,O
wait,O
until,O
you,O
see,O
what,O
’,O
s,O
coming,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
“,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
care,O
what,O
state,O
you,O
’,O
re,O
in,O
",",O
this,O
computer,O
voting,O
system,O
is,O
wide,O
open,O
to,O
fraud,O
and,O
intervention,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
lou,PER_B
##do,PER_I
##bb,PER_I
##s,PER_I
true,O
",",O
and,O
wait,O
until,O
you,O
see,O
what,O
’,O
s,O
coming,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
wo,O
##w,O
!,O
twitter,ORG_B
ban,O
##s,O
highly,O
respected,O
pennsylvania,O
state,O
sen,O
##ator,O
doug,PER_B
mast,PER_I
##rian,PER_I
##o,PER_I
after,O
he,O
did,O
a,O
great,O
job,O
of,O
leading,O
a,O
hearing,O
on,O
the,O
2020,O
election,O
fraud,O
.,O
they,O
and,O
the,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
",",O
working,O
together,O
",",O
want,O
to,O
sil,O
##ence,O
the,O
truth,O
.,O
can,O
’,O
t,O
let,O
that,O
happen,O
.,O
this,O
is,O
what,O
comm,O
##uni,O
##st,O
countries,O
do,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
big,O
news,O
:,O
pennsylvania,O
poll,O
watche,O
##r,O
:,O
usb,O
drives,O
upl,O
##oad,O
##ed,O
to,O
machines,O
",",O
gave,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
thousands,O
of,O
votes,O
.,O
says,O
47,O
usb,O
drives,O
are,O
now,O
missing,O
.,O
every,O
upl,O
##oad,O
gave,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
50,O
",",O
000,O
votes,O
.,O
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
“,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
nominate,O
##s,O
record,O
number,O
of,O
federal,O
judge,O
##s,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
but,O
how,O
many,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
were,O
fraudulent,O
##ly,O
cast,O
for,O
the,O
dem,ORG_B
##s,ORG_I
?,O
did,O
people,O
vote,O
after,O
the,O
election,O
had,O
ended,O
?,O
did,O
officials,O
actually,O
not,O
allow,O
observe,O
##rs,O
and,O
poll,O
watche,O
##rs,O
to,O
look,O
for,O
an,O
honest,O
count,O
?,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
debate,O
poll,O
average,O
:,O
89,O
%,O
trump,PER_B
.,O
11,O
%,O
sleep,O
##y,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
andrew,PER_B
mcca,PER_I
##be,PER_I
was,O
exposed,O
for,O
who,O
he,O
is,O
today,O
in,O
the,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
senate,O
.,O
he,O
was,O
totally,O
destroye,O
##d,O
-,O
an,O
ig,O
##nor,O
##ant,O
fo,O
##ol,O
.,O
the,O
great,O
people,O
of,O
the,O
fb,ORG_B
##i,ORG_I
must,O
make,O
sure,O
that,O
he,O
and,O
his,O
former,O
boss,O
",",O
james,PER_B
come,PER_I
##y,PER_I
",",O
pay,O
the,O
price,O
for,O
what,O
they,O
have,O
done,O
to,O
the,O
reputation,O
of,O
the,O
fb,ORG_B
##i,ORG_I
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
gi,PER_B
##uli,PER_I
##ani,PER_I
:,O
the,O
case,O
for,O
election,O
fraud,O
being,O
made,O
by,O
americans,O
via,O
@,O
bre,ORG_B
##it,ORG_I
##bar,ORG_I
##tn,ORG_I
##ew,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-29,O
remember,O
republic,PER_B
##ans,PER_I
",",O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
already,O
had,O
17,O
witness,O
##es,O
",",O
we,O
were,O
given,O
none,O
!,O
witness,O
##es,O
are,O
up,O
to,O
the,O
house,O
",",O
not,O
up,O
to,O
the,O
senate,O
.,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
let,O
the,O
dem,PER_B
##s,PER_I
play,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-07-12,O
thank,O
you,O
lar,PER_B
##a,PER_I
and,O
jess,PER_B
##ie,PER_I
jane,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-07-02,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
texas,PER_B
will,O
defend,O
them,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
indemnify,O
them,O
against,O
political,O
har,O
##ass,O
##ment,O
by,O
new,ORG_B
york,ORG_I
state,O
and,O
governor,O
cu,PER_B
##omo,PER_I
.,O
so,O
many,O
people,O
are,O
leaving,O
new,LOC_B
york,LOC_I
for,O
texas,LOC_B
and,O
florida,LOC_B
that,O
it,O
is,O
totally,O
under,O
sieg,O
##e,O
.,O
first,O
new,LOC_B
york,LOC_I
taxes,O
you,O
too,O
high,O
",",O
then,O
they,O
sue,O
you,O
",",O
just,O
to,O
complete,O
the,O
job,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-13,O
happy,O
birth,O
##day,O
!,O
#,O
guard,PER_B
##38,PER_I
##3,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-04-20,O
i,O
will,O
be,O
having,O
a,O
white,O
house,O
press,O
conference,O
today,O
at,O
5,O
:,O
30,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-09,O
great,O
new,O
book,O
by,O
sarah,PER_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-07-29,O
the,O
biggest,O
and,O
best,O
results,O
coming,O
out,O
of,O
the,O
good,O
gdp,O
report,O
was,O
that,O
the,O
quarterly,O
trade,O
deficit,O
has,O
been,O
reduced,O
by,O
$,O
52,O
billion,O
and,O
",",O
of,O
course,O
",",O
the,O
historically,O
low,O
unemployment,O
numbers,O
",",O
especially,O
for,O
african,O
americans,O
",",O
hispanic,O
##s,O
",",O
asian,O
##s,O
and,O
women,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-08-21,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
all,O
je,O
##ws,O
",",O
black,O
##s,O
",",O
ga,O
##ys,O
",",O
everyone,O
.,O
and,O
importantly,O
",",O
he,O
’,O
s,O
good,O
for,O
everyone,O
in,O
america,O
who,O
wants,O
a,O
job,O
.,O
”,O
wo,O
##w,O
!,O
@,O
news,ORG_B
##max,ORG_I
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##and,ORG_I
##frie,ORG_I
##nds,ORG_I
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2017-08-27,O
historic,O
rain,O
##fall,O
in,O
houston,LOC_B
",",O
and,O
all,O
over,O
texas,LOC_B
.,O
floods,O
are,O
unprecedented,O
",",O
and,O
more,O
rain,O
coming,O
.,O
spirit,O
of,O
the,O
people,O
is,O
incredible,O
.,O
thanks,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-06-19,O
if,O
the,O
dem,PER_B
##s,PER_I
get,O
in,O
",",O
our,O
country,O
is,O
in,O
big,O
trouble,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-09-26,O
a,O
few,O
of,O
the,O
many,O
clip,O
##s,O
of,O
john,PER_B
mcca,PER_I
##in,PER_I
talking,O
about,O
repeal,O
##ing,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
replacing,O
o,O
',O
care,O
.,O
my,O
oh,O
my,O
has,O
he,O
changed,O
-,O
complete,O
turn,O
from,O
years,O
of,O
talk,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-04-12,O
the,O
big,O
oil,O
deal,O
with,O
opec,ORG_B
plus,O
is,O
done,O
.,O
this,O
will,O
save,O
hundreds,O
of,O
thousands,O
of,O
energy,O
jobs,O
in,O
the,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
.,O
i,O
would,O
like,O
to,O
thank,O
and,O
congr,O
##atu,O
##late,O
president,O
put,PER_B
##in,PER_I
of,O
russia,LOC_B
and,O
king,O
sal,PER_B
##man,PER_I
of,O
saudi,LOC_B
arabia,LOC_I
.,O
i,O
just,O
spoke,O
to,O
them,O
from,O
the,O
ova,O
##l,O
office,O
.,O
great,O
deal,O
for,O
all,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-09,O
drain,O
the,O
swa,O
##mp,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-22,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
are,O
only,O
interested,O
in,O
bail,O
##ing,O
out,O
their,O
bad,O
##ly,O
managed,O
",",O
high,O
crime,O
",",O
blue,O
states,O
.,O
they,O
are,O
not,O
interested,O
in,O
our,O
workers,O
or,O
small,O
businesses,O
.,O
cra,O
##zy,O
nancy,PER_B
will,O
only,O
do,O
stimulus,O
",",O
which,O
would,O
be,O
helpful,O
",",O
if,O
we,O
couple,O
it,O
with,O
bail,O
##out,O
money,O
.,O
republic,O
##an,O
states,O
are,O
great,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-20,O
jim,PER_B
",",O
to,O
late,O
to,O
take,O
it,O
back,O
.,O
stay,O
with,O
the,O
truth,O
",",O
no,O
pand,O
##ering,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-05-24,O
you,O
are,O
right,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-29,O
this,O
has,O
been,O
an,O
incredible,O
couple,O
of,O
weeks,O
for,O
america,PER_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-14,O
if,O
you,O
mur,O
##der,O
a,O
police,O
officer,O
",",O
you,O
should,O
receive,O
the,O
death,O
penalty,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-03-07,O
our,O
wonderful,O
new,O
healthcare,O
bill,O
is,O
now,O
out,O
for,O
review,O
and,O
negotiation,O
.,O
obama,O
##care,O
is,O
a,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
disaster,O
-,O
is,O
imp,O
##lo,O
##ding,O
fast,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-10-19,O
workers,O
of,O
firm,O
involved,O
with,O
the,O
discr,O
##edit,O
##ed,O
and,O
fa,O
##ke,O
dos,O
##sie,O
##r,O
take,O
the,O
5th,O
.,O
who,O
paid,O
for,O
it,O
",",O
russia,O
",",O
the,O
fb,O
##i,O
or,O
the,O
dem,O
##s,O
(,O
or,O
all,O
),O
?,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-06-12,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
the,O
fa,O
##ke,O
(,O
corrupt,O
),O
news,O
media,O
said,O
they,O
had,O
a,O
leak,O
into,O
poll,O
##ing,O
done,O
by,O
my,O
campaign,O
which,O
",",O
by,O
the,O
way,O
and,O
despite,O
the,O
pho,O
##ny,O
and,O
never,O
ending,O
wit,O
##ch,O
hunt,O
",",O
are,O
the,O
best,O
numbers,O
we,O
have,O
ever,O
had,O
.,O
they,O
reported,O
fa,O
##ke,O
numbers,O
that,O
they,O
made,O
up,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
don,O
’,O
t,O
even,O
exist,O
.,O
we,O
will,O
win,O
again,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-10,O
wo,O
##w,O
",",O
thank,O
you,O
minn,PER_B
##eap,PER_I
##olis,PER_I
",",O
minnesota,PER_B
—,O
on,O
my,O
way,O
!,O
#,O
ka,O
##g,O
##202,O
##0,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-22,O
"""",O
schi,PER_B
##ff,PER_I
',PER_I
s,PER_I
"""",O
"""",O
fact,O
"""",O
"""",O
witness,O
##es,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-01-09,O
rup,PER_B
##ert,PER_I
mur,PER_I
##doc,PER_I
##h,PER_I
is,O
a,O
great,O
guy,O
who,O
likes,O
me,O
much,O
better,O
as,O
a,O
very,O
successful,O
candidate,O
than,O
he,O
ever,O
did,O
as,O
a,O
very,O
successful,O
developer,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-09-13,O
sen,O
##ator,O
deb,PER_B
##bie,PER_I
sta,PER_I
##ben,PER_I
##ow,PER_I
and,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
are,O
totally,O
against,O
approving,O
the,O
farm,O
bill,O
.,O
they,O
are,O
fighting,O
tooth,O
and,O
nail,O
to,O
not,O
allow,O
our,O
great,O
farmers,O
to,O
get,O
what,O
they,O
so,O
rich,O
##ly,O
deserve,O
.,O
work,O
requirements,O
are,O
imperative,O
and,O
the,O
dem,PER_B
##s,PER_I
are,O
a,O
no,O
.,O
not,O
good,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-07-07,O
big,O
decision,O
will,O
soon,O
be,O
made,O
on,O
our,O
next,O
justice,O
of,O
the,O
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-07-02,O
darr,PER_B
##ell,PER_I
always,O
has,O
had,O
my,O
full,O
support,O
and,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
.,O
we,O
need,O
him,O
bad,O
##ly,O
in,O
washington,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-25,O
so,O
great,O
that,O
oil,O
prices,O
are,O
falling,O
(,O
thank,O
you,O
president,O
t,O
),O
.,O
add,O
that,O
",",O
which,O
is,O
like,O
a,O
big,O
tax,O
cut,O
",",O
to,O
our,O
other,O
good,O
economic,O
news,O
.,O
inflation,O
down,O
(,O
are,O
you,O
listening,O
fed,ORG_B
),O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-12-21,O
today,O
",",O
it,O
was,O
my,O
honor,O
to,O
sign,O
into,O
law,O
h,O
.,O
r,O
.,O
72,O
##13,O
",",O
the,O
“,O
counter,O
##ing,O
weapons,O
of,O
mass,O
destruction,O
act,O
of,O
2018,O
.,O
”,O
the,O
act,O
redesign,O
##ates,O
the,O
@,O
dh,PER_B
##sg,PER_I
##ov,PER_I
domestic,O
nuclear,O
detection,O
office,O
as,O
the,O
counter,O
##ing,O
weapons,O
of,O
mass,O
destruction,O
office,O
.,O
read,O
more,O
:,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-29,O
failed,O
rin,PER_B
##o,PER_I
former,O
governor,O
rick,PER_B
sn,PER_I
##yde,PER_I
##r,PER_I
of,O
michigan,LOC_B
was,O
a,O
disaster,O
with,O
respect,O
to,O
the,O
fli,O
##nt,O
water,O
catastrophe,O
",",O
and,O
a,O
very,O
bad,O
governor,O
overall,O
.,O
he,O
hurt,O
so,O
many,O
people,O
with,O
his,O
gross,O
incom,O
##pet,O
##ence,O
.,O
he,O
remind,O
##s,O
me,O
of,O
sleep,O
##y,O
joe,PER_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-20,O
just,O
arrived,O
in,O
colorado,LOC_B
",",O
see,O
everyone,O
soon,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-15,O
progress,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-04-24,O
great,O
conversation,O
with,O
president,O
len,PER_B
##in,PER_I
more,PER_I
##no,PER_I
of,O
the,O
republic,LOC_B
of,LOC_I
ecuador,LOC_I
.,O
we,O
will,O
be,O
sending,O
them,O
des,O
##perat,O
##ely,O
needed,O
venti,O
##lator,O
##s,O
",",O
of,O
which,O
we,O
have,O
recently,O
manufactured,O
many,O
",",O
and,O
helping,O
them,O
in,O
other,O
ways,O
.,O
they,O
are,O
fighting,O
hard,O
against,O
coro,O
##nav,O
##ir,O
##us,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-06-09,O
“,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
&,O
amp,O
;,O
activis,O
##ts,O
call,O
to,O
def,O
##und,O
police,O
departments,O
.,O
they,O
’,O
ve,O
gone,O
so,O
far,O
left,O
that,O
they,O
eat,O
their,O
young,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
mira,PER_B
##nda,PER_I
##dev,PER_I
##ine,PER_I
@,O
ny,ORG_B
##post,ORG_I
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##and,O
##frie,O
##nds,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-05,O
detroit,LOC_B
absent,O
##ee,O
ball,O
##ot,O
counting,O
cha,O
##os,O
",",O
blocke,O
##d,O
windows,O
and,O
observe,O
##rs,O
via,O
@,O
bre,ORG_B
##it,ORG_I
##bar,ORG_I
##tn,ORG_I
##ew,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-05-03,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
got,O
it,O
wrong,O
again,O
",",O
as,O
always,O
",",O
and,O
tens,O
of,O
thousands,O
of,O
lives,O
were,O
save,O
##d,O
by,O
my,O
early,O
ban,O
of,O
china,LOC_B
into,O
our,O
country,O
.,O
the,O
people,O
that,O
we,O
’,O
re,O
allowed,O
were,O
heavily,O
scru,O
##tini,O
##zed,O
and,O
tested,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
citizens,O
",",O
and,O
as,O
such,O
",",O
i,O
welcome,O
them,O
with,O
open,O
arms,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-18,O
on,O
national,O
po,O
##w,O
/,O
mi,O
##a,O
recognition,O
day,O
",",O
the,O
@,O
flo,PER_B
##tus,PER_I
and,O
i,O
honor,O
the,O
men,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
women,O
of,O
our,O
armed,O
forces,O
who,O
have,O
self,O
##less,O
##ly,O
served,O
our,O
country,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
made,O
tremendous,O
sacrific,O
##es,O
to,O
defend,O
our,O
liberty,O
.,O
our,O
nation,O
remains,O
committed,O
to,O
accounting,O
for,O
all,O
missing,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-03-28,O
why,O
is,O
##n,O
',O
t,O
the,O
house,ORG_B
intelligence,ORG_I
committee,ORG_I
looking,O
into,O
the,O
bill,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
deal,O
that,O
allowed,O
big,O
uranium,O
to,O
go,O
to,O
russia,LOC_B
",",O
russian,O
speech,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-29,O
beaut,O
##if,O
##ul,O
#,O
mag,O
##ara,O
##lly,O
ton,O
##ight,O
in,O
grand,O
rapid,O
##s,O
",",O
michigan,PER_B
-,O
thank,O
you,O
",",O
i,O
love,O
you,O
!,O
make,O
america,LOC_B
great,O
again,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-12-20,O
congress,O
just,O
passed,O
the,O
criminal,O
justice,O
reform,O
bill,O
known,O
as,O
the,O
#,O
first,O
##ste,O
##pac,O
##t,O
.,O
congratulations,O
!,O
this,O
is,O
a,O
great,O
bi,O
-,O
part,O
##isa,O
##n,O
achievement,O
for,O
everybody,O
.,O
when,O
both,O
parties,O
work,O
together,O
we,O
can,O
keep,O
our,O
country,O
safer,O
.,O
a,O
wonderful,O
thing,O
for,O
the,O
u,LOC_B
.,LOC_I
s,LOC_I
.,LOC_I
a,LOC_I
.,LOC_I
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-15,O
so,O
now,O
come,O
##y,O
’,O
s,O
admit,O
##ting,O
he,O
was,O
wrong,O
.,O
wo,O
##w,O
",",O
but,O
he,O
’,O
s,O
only,O
doing,O
so,O
because,O
he,O
got,O
caught,O
red,O
hand,O
##ed,O
.,O
he,O
was,O
actually,O
caught,O
a,O
long,O
time,O
ago,O
.,O
so,O
what,O
are,O
the,O
consequences,O
for,O
his,O
unlawful,O
conduct,O
.,O
could,O
it,O
be,O
years,O
in,O
jai,O
##l,O
?,O
where,O
are,O
the,O
apol,O
##ogie,O
##s,O
to,O
me,O
and,O
others,O
",",O
jim,PER_B
?,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-08-10,O
"""",O
"""",O
"""",O
trump,PER_B
approval,O
rebound,O
##s,O
to,O
45,O
%,O
",",O
surge,O
##s,O
among,O
hispanic,O
##s,O
",",O
union,O
homes,O
",",O
men,O
"""",O
"""",O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-31,O
paul,PER_B
ryan,PER_I
should,O
be,O
focusing,O
on,O
holding,O
the,O
majority,O
rather,O
than,O
giving,O
his,O
opinions,O
on,O
birth,O
##right,O
citizens,O
##hip,O
",",O
something,O
he,O
knows,O
nothing,O
about,O
!,O
our,O
new,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
majority,O
will,O
work,O
on,O
this,O
",",O
closing,O
the,O
immigration,O
loop,O
##hole,O
##s,O
and,O
securing,O
our,O
border,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-08-13,O
just,O
fired,O
agent,O
str,PER_B
##zo,PER_I
##k,PER_I
",",O
formerly,O
of,O
the,O
fb,ORG_B
##i,ORG_I
",",O
was,O
in,O
charge,O
of,O
the,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
clint,PER_I
##on,PER_I
sham,O
investigation,O
.,O
it,O
was,O
a,O
total,O
fraud,O
on,O
the,O
american,O
public,O
and,O
should,O
be,O
properly,O
red,O
##one,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-08-31,O
while,O
made,PER_B
##lei,PER_I
##ne,PER_I
west,PER_I
##er,PER_I
##hou,PER_I
##t,PER_I
has,O
a,O
fully,O
enforceable,O
confidentiality,O
agreement,O
",",O
she,O
is,O
a,O
very,O
good,O
person,O
and,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
think,O
there,O
would,O
ever,O
be,O
reason,O
to,O
use,O
it,O
.,O
she,O
called,O
me,O
yesterday,O
to,O
apologize,O
",",O
had,O
a,O
bad,O
night,O
.,O
i,O
fully,O
understood,O
and,O
for,O
##ga,O
##ve,O
her,O
!,O
i,O
love,O
tiffany,PER_B
",",O
doing,O
great,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-12,O
louisiana,PER_B
—,O
tomorrow,O
",",O
you,O
will,O
head,O
to,O
the,O
poll,O
##s,O
and,O
vote,O
to,O
replace,O
libera,O
##l,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##t,O
john,O
bel,O
edwards,O
with,O
a,O
great,O
new,O
republic,O
##an,O
governor,O
!,O
get,O
out,O
and,O
vote,O
for,O
either,O
@,O
doc,PER_B
##abr,PER_I
##ah,PER_I
##am,PER_I
or,O
@,O
edd,PER_B
##ier,PER_I
##is,PER_I
##pon,PER_I
##e,PER_I
(,O
both,O
great,O
),O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-04-06,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
it,O
’,O
s,O
powerful,O
common,O
sense,O
immigration,O
laws,O
to,O
stop,O
illegal,O
##s,O
from,O
coming,O
through,O
mexico,LOC_B
into,O
the,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
",",O
and,O
removing,O
them,O
back,O
to,O
their,O
country,O
of,O
origin,O
.,O
until,O
mexico,ORG_B
clean,O
##s,O
up,O
this,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
massive,O
migration,O
",",O
we,O
will,O
be,O
focusing,O
on,O
border,O
security,O
",",O
not,O
ports,O
of,O
entry,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-05-10,O
gin,PER_B
##a,PER_I
has,PER_I
##pel,PER_I
did,O
a,O
spectac,O
##ular,O
job,O
today,O
.,O
there,O
is,O
nobody,O
even,O
close,O
to,O
run,O
the,O
cia,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-04-18,O
presidential,O
har,O
##ass,O
##ment,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-05-17,O
ph,PER_B
##yl,PER_I
##lis,PER_I
george,PER_I
was,O
a,O
great,O
person,O
and,O
a,O
true,O
pioneer,O
for,O
women,O
in,O
television,O
.,O
the,O
nfl,O
could,O
not,O
have,O
made,O
a,O
better,O
“,O
pick,O
”,O
when,O
they,O
choose,O
ph,PER_B
##yl,PER_I
##lis,PER_I
to,O
be,O
the,O
first,O
wo,O
##man,O
to,O
represent,O
them,O
.,O
also,O
",",O
a,O
wonderful,O
first,O
lad,O
##y,O
of,O
kentucky,LOC_B
as,O
the,O
wi,O
##fe,O
of,O
gov,O
.,O
john,PER_B
y,PER_I
.,PER_I
brown,PER_I
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
report,O
:,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
’,O
s,O
thanksgiving,O
day,O
address,O
gets,O
just,O
1000,O
views,O
online,O
",",O
a,O
record,O
low,O
.,O
observe,O
##rs,O
say,O
a,O
candidate,PER_B
with,O
“,O
80,O
",",O
000,O
",",O
000,O
”,O
votes,O
would,O
get,O
many,O
more,O
online,O
viewers,O
.,O
numbers,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
lie,O
",",O
or,O
add,O
up,O
!,O
@,O
oa,O
##nn,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
that,O
’,O
s,O
why,O
mike,PER_B
was,O
number,O
one,O
in,O
his,O
class,O
at,O
west,ORG_B
point,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
thanks,O
dan,PER_B
.,O
big,O
win,O
for,O
us,O
in,O
texas,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
news,O
conference,O
on,O
reduced,O
drug,O
prices,O
at,O
2,O
:,O
30,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
he,O
should,O
pay,O
a,O
big,O
price,O
for,O
his,O
sub,O
##versi,O
##on,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
“,O
statistical,O
sampling,O
to,O
prove,O
widespread,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
multiple,O
accounts,O
of,O
fraud,O
and,O
voting,O
irregular,O
##ities,O
may,O
overtur,O
##n,O
election,O
”,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
call,O
for,O
paper,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
.,O
@,O
rand,PER_B
##pa,PER_I
##ul,PER_I
@,O
oa,ORG_B
##nn,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
our,O
economy,O
is,O
doing,O
great,O
",",O
and,O
is,O
ready,O
to,O
set,O
new,O
records,O
-,O
best,O
ever,O
(,O
again,O
!,O
),O
.,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
will,O
destroy,O
everything,O
with,O
his,O
massive,O
tax,O
increases,O
.,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
let,O
it,O
happen,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
a,O
brav,O
##e,O
patriot,O
.,O
more,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
more,O
people,O
are,O
stepping,O
forward,O
to,O
expose,O
this,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
#,O
vote,O
##ear,O
##ly,O
##day,O
#,O
[UNK],ORG_B
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
the,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
is,O
talking,O
about,O
cases,O
",",O
cases,O
",",O
cases,O
.,O
this,O
includes,O
many,O
low,O
risk,O
people,O
.,O
media,ORG_B
is,O
doing,O
everything,O
possible,O
to,O
create,O
fear,O
prior,O
to,O
november,O
3rd,O
.,O
the,O
cases,O
are,O
up,O
because,O
testing,O
is,O
way,O
up,O
",",O
by,O
far,O
the,O
most,O
",",O
and,O
best,O
",",O
in,O
the,O
world,O
.,O
mortality,O
rate,O
is,O
down,O
85,O
%,O
plus,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
why,O
won,O
’,O
t,O
they,O
do,O
it,O
",",O
and,O
why,O
are,O
they,O
so,O
fast,O
to,O
certify,O
a,O
meaning,O
##less,O
tall,O
##y,O
?,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-20,O
the,O
governor,ORG_B
of,
georgia,LOC_B
",",O
and,O
secretary,ORG_B
of,ORG_I
state,ORG_I
",",O
refuse,O
to,O
let,O
us,O
look,O
at,O
signature,O
##s,O
which,O
would,O
expose,O
hundreds,O
of,O
thousands,O
of,O
illegal,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
give,O
the,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
party,ORG_I
and,O
me,O
",",O
david,PER_B
per,PER_I
##due,PER_I
",",O
and,O
perhaps,O
kelly,PER_B
loe,PER_I
##ffle,PER_I
##r,PER_I
",",O
a,O
big,O
victory,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
if,O
i,O
do,O
not,O
sound,O
like,O
a,O
typical,O
washington,LOC_B
polit,O
##icia,O
##n,O
",",O
it,O
’,O
s,O
because,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
not,O
a,O
polit,O
##icia,O
##n,O
.,O
if,O
i,O
do,O
not,O
always,O
play,O
by,O
the,O
rules,O
of,O
the,O
washington,ORG_B
establishment,ORG_I
",",O
it,O
’,O
s,O
because,O
i,O
was,O
elected,O
to,O
fight,O
for,O
you,O
",",O
harder,O
than,O
anyone,O
ever,O
has,O
before,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
i,O
could,O
not,O
sit,O
by,O
and,O
watch,O
them,O
take,O
advantage,O
of,O
you,O
anymore,O
.,O
they,O
are,O
coming,O
after,O
me,O
because,O
i,O
am,O
standing,O
in,O
their,O
way,O
",",O
and,O
standing,O
guard,O
for,O
this,O
country,LOC_B
we,O
love,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
for,O
years,O
",",O
i,O
watche,O
##d,O
one,O
bet,O
##ray,O
##al,O
after,O
another,O
",",O
as,O
polit,O
##icia,O
##ns,O
like,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
sold,O
out,O
american,O
workers,O
at,O
every,O
turn,O
—,O
sha,O
##tter,O
##ing,O
the,O
lives,O
of,O
millions,O
of,O
american,O
families,O
while,O
their,O
families,O
rake,O
##d,O
in,O
millions,O
of,O
dollars,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
is,O
a,O
corrupt,O
polit,O
##icia,O
##n,O
and,O
he,O
’,O
s,O
compromised,O
.,O
china,LOC_B
is,O
des,O
##perat,O
##e,O
for,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
to,O
win,O
because,O
if,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
wins,O
",",O
china,LOC_B
wins,O
–,O
and,O
china,LOC_B
will,O
own,O
america,LOC_B
.,O
this,O
corruption,O
is,O
exactly,O
why,O
i,O
decided,O
to,O
run,O
for,O
president,O
in,O
the,O
first,O
place,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
thank,O
you,O
to,O
all,O
of,O
the,O
great,O
american,O
patriot,O
##s,O
in,O
the,O
village,O
##s,O
",",O
florida,ORG_B
!,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
on,O
the,O
37,O
##th,O
anniversary,O
of,O
the,O
hor,O
##ren,O
##do,O
##us,O
attack,O
on,O
our,O
united,O
states,O
marine,O
##s,O
",",O
sail,O
##ors,O
",",O
and,O
sold,O
##ier,O
##s,O
in,O
be,LOC_B
##ir,LOC_I
##ut,LOC_I
",",O
we,O
honor,O
the,O
241,O
hero,O
##es,O
who,O
lost,O
their,O
lives,O
that,O
day,O
.,O
we,O
will,O
never,O
forget,O
them,O
.,O
sem,O
##per,O
fi,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
i,O
was,O
in,O
philadelphia,ORG_B
watching,O
fraud,O
happen,O
.,O
here,O
’,O
s,O
how,O
it,O
went,O
down,O
they,O
shut,O
out,O
our,O
poll,O
watche,O
##rs,O
and,O
observe,O
##rs,O
.,O
those,O
hundreds,O
of,O
thousands,O
of,O
votes,O
should,O
not,O
be,O
allowed,O
.,O
corrupt,O
polit,O
##ics,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
’,O
s,O
response,O
to,O
the,O
h1,O
##n1,O
swin,O
##e,O
flu,O
",",O
far,O
less,O
let,O
##hal,O
than,O
cov,O
##id,O
19,O
",",O
was,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
weakest,O
and,O
worst,O
in,O
the,O
history,O
of,O
fighting,O
epidemic,O
##s,O
and,O
pandemic,O
##s,O
.,O
it,O
was,O
path,O
##etic,O
",",O
those,O
involved,O
have,O
said,O
.,O
joe,PER_B
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
have,O
a,O
clu,O
##e,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
the,O
georgia,LOC_B
reco,O
##unt,O
is,O
a,O
jo,O
##ke,O
and,O
is,O
being,O
done,O
under,O
protest,O
.,O
even,O
though,O
thousands,O
of,O
fraudulent,O
votes,O
have,O
been,O
found,O
",",O
the,O
real,O
number,O
is,O
in,O
matching,O
signature,O
##s,O
.,O
governor,ORG_B
must,O
open,O
up,O
the,O
uncon,O
##stitut,O
##ional,O
consent,O
decree,O
and,O
call,O
in,O
the,O
legislature,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
they,O
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
even,O
allow,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
observe,O
##rs,O
into,O
the,O
building,O
to,O
watch,O
.,O
a,O
terribl,O
##e,O
ins,O
##ult,O
to,O
our,O
constitution,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
“,O
the,O
numbers,O
have,O
not,O
improved,O
",",O
it,O
is,O
still,O
71,O
%,O
out,O
of,O
balance,O
”,O
",",O
stated,O
wayne,LOC_B
county,LOC_I
",",O
michigan,LOC_B
",",O
can,O
##vas,O
##ser,O
##s,O
.,O
“,O
there,O
is,O
widespread,O
irregular,O
##ities,O
in,O
poll,O
numbers,O
.,O
”,O
there,O
are,O
“,O
more,O
votes,O
than,O
people,O
”,O
.,O
the,O
two,O
har,O
##asse,O
##d,O
patriot,O
can,O
##vas,O
##ser,O
##s,O
refuse,O
to,O
sign,O
the,O
papers,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
.,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##par,PER_I
##nel,PER_I
##lus,PER_I
##a,PER_I
is,O
a,O
bright,O
star,O
for,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
.,O
military,O
",",O
vet,O
##s,O
",",O
low,O
taxes,O
and,O
your,O
2nd,O
amendment,O
will,O
be,O
totally,O
protected,O
.,O
his,O
opp,O
##onent,O
is,O
a,O
weak,O
and,O
ineffective,O
pu,O
##ppe,O
##t,O
for,O
pel,PER_B
##osi,PER_I
and,O
her,O
new,O
radical,O
left,O
friends,O
.,O
vote,O
for,O
sean,PER_B
par,PER_I
##nel,PER_I
##l,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
obama,PER_B
spi,O
##ed,O
on,O
our,O
campaign,O
-,O
and,O
got,O
caught,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
so,O
important,O
to,O
vote,O
for,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_I
in,O
the,O
house,O
.,O
break,O
away,O
from,O
pel,PER_B
##osi,PER_I
and,O
her,O
high,O
taxing,O
new,O
radical,O
left,O
friends,O
.,O
protect,O
your,O
2nd,O
amendment,O
",",O
military,O
",",O
vet,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
so,O
##oo,O
much,O
more,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-11,O
people,O
will,O
not,O
accept,O
this,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
no,O
",",O
the,O
2020,O
election,O
was,O
a,O
total,O
sca,O
##m,O
",",O
we,O
won,O
by,O
a,O
lot,O
(,O
and,O
will,O
hopefully,O
turn,O
over,O
the,O
fraudulent,O
result,O
),O
",",O
but,O
we,O
must,O
get,O
out,O
and,O
help,O
david,PER_B
and,O
kelly,PER_B
",",O
two,O
great,O
people,O
.,O
otherwise,O
we,O
are,O
playing,O
right,O
into,O
the,O
hands,O
of,O
some,O
very,O
sick,O
people,O
.,O
i,O
will,O
be,O
in,O
georgia,LOC_B
on,O
saturday,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
pennsylvania,ORG_B
ball,O
##ot,O
“,O
mistake,O
##s,O
”,O
made,O
",",O
in,O
my,O
opinion,O
",",O
on,O
purpose,O
by,O
the,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##t,O
governor,ORG_B
",",O
puts,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_B
",",O
in,O
particular,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##par,PER_I
##nel,PER_I
##lus,PER_I
##a,PER_I
",",O
at,O
great,O
risk,O
.,O
corrupt,O
polit,O
##ics,O
in,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
must,O
be,O
investigated,O
immediately,O
.,O
by,O
the,O
way,O
",",O
philadelphia,LOC_B
is,O
out,O
of,O
control,O
.,O
@,O
the,ORG_B
##just,ORG_I
##iced,ORG_I
##ept,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-17,O
this,O
says,O
it,O
all,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-17,O
i,O
have,O
reversed,O
the,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
decision,O
to,O
cancel,O
wre,O
##ath,O
##s,O
across,O
america,LOC_B
at,O
arl,LOC_B
##ington,LOC_I
national,LOC_I
cemetery,LOC_I
.,O
it,O
will,O
now,O
go,O
on,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
the,O
recent,O
statement,O
by,O
chris,PER_B
kre,PER_I
##bs,PER_I
on,O
the,O
security,O
of,O
the,O
2020,O
election,O
was,O
highly,O
inaccurate,O
",",O
in,O
that,O
there,O
were,O
massive,O
impr,O
##opri,O
##eti,O
##es,O
and,O
fraud,O
-,O
including,O
dead,O
people,O
voting,O
",",O
poll,O
watche,O
##rs,O
not,O
allowed,O
into,O
poll,O
##ing,O
locations,O
",",O
“,O
gli,O
##tche,O
##s,O
”,O
in,O
the,O
voting,O
machines,O
which,O
changed,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
yesterday,O
’,O
s,O
news,O
conference,O
being,O
broadcast,O
in,O
full,O
now,O
on,O
@,O
news,ORG_B
##max,ORG_I
.,O
enjoy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
have,O
a,O
great,O
“,O
mag,O
##a,O
-,O
gras,O
”,O
rally,O
today,O
on,O
our,O
wonderful,O
long,O
island,O
.,O
cut,O
taxes,O
",",O
stop,O
crime,O
",",O
vote,O
for,O
trump,PER_B
.,O
our,O
city,O
and,O
state,O
are,O
a,O
mess,O
.,O
what,O
do,O
you,O
have,O
to,O
lose,O
?,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
congratulations,O
to,O
@,O
sen,PER_B
##ron,PER_I
##jo,PER_I
##hn,PER_I
##son,PER_I
for,O
his,O
dog,O
##ged,O
pursuit,O
",",O
as,O
chairman,ORG_B
of,ORG_B
homeland,ORG_B
",",O
of,O
political,O
corruption,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
important,O
news,O
conference,O
today,O
by,O
lawyer,O
##s,O
on,O
a,O
very,O
clear,O
and,O
viable,O
path,O
to,O
victory,O
.,O
pieces,O
are,O
very,O
nicely,O
falling,O
into,O
place,O
.,O
rn,O
##c,O
at,O
12,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
all,O
newly,O
rebu,O
##ilt,O
military,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
thank,O
you,O
new,PER_B
hampshire,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
amazing,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
big,O
victory,O
moments,O
ago,O
in,O
the,O
state,LOC_B
of,LOC_I
nevada,LOC_I
.,O
the,O
all,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##t,O
county,O
commissioner,O
race,O
",",O
on,O
same,O
ball,O
##ot,O
as,O
president,PER_B
",",O
just,O
throw,O
##n,O
out,O
because,O
of,O
large,O
scale,O
vote,O
##r,O
discrepanc,O
##y,O
.,O
clark,O
county,O
officials,O
do,O
not,O
have,O
confidence,O
in,O
their,O
own,O
election,O
security,O
.,O
major,O
impact,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
they,O
would,O
’,O
nt,O
let,O
republic,O
##an,O
poll,O
watche,O
##rs,O
into,O
the,O
counting,O
rooms,O
.,O
uncon,O
##stitut,O
##ional,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
wrong,O
!,O
at,O
first,O
they,O
voted,O
against,O
because,O
there,O
were,O
far,O
more,O
votes,O
than,O
people,O
(,O
sad,O
!,O
),O
.,O
then,O
they,O
were,O
threatened,O
",",O
scr,O
##ea,O
##med,O
at,O
and,O
vic,O
##ious,O
##ly,O
har,O
##asse,O
##d,O
",",O
and,O
were,O
forced,O
to,O
change,O
their,O
vote,O
",",O
but,O
then,O
refuse,O
##d,O
",",O
as,O
american,O
patriot,O
##s,O
",",O
to,O
sign,O
the,O
documents,O
.,O
71,O
%,O
mess,O
.,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
har,O
##ass,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
the,O
only,O
thing,O
secure,O
about,O
our,O
2020,O
election,O
was,O
that,O
it,O
was,O
virtually,O
impe,O
##net,O
##rable,O
by,O
foreign,O
powers,O
.,O
on,O
that,O
",",O
the,O
trump,ORG_B
administration,ORG_I
takes,O
great,O
credit,O
.,O
unfortunately,O
",",O
the,O
radical,O
left,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
",",O
dominion,O
",",O
and,O
others,O
",",O
were,O
perhaps,O
more,O
successful,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
votes,O
from,O
trump,PER_B
to,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
",",O
late,O
voting,O
",",O
and,O
many,O
more,O
.,O
therefore,O
",",O
effective,O
immediately,O
",",O
chris,PER_B
kre,PER_I
##bs,PER_I
has,O
been,O
terminated,O
as,O
director,O
of,O
the,O
cybersecurity,ORG_B
and,ORG_I
infrastructure,ORG_I
security,ORG_I
agency,ORG_I
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-17,O
“,O
dead,O
people,O
voted,O
”,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-27,O
so,O
much,O
truth,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
well,O
",",O
it,O
’,O
s,O
really,O
quite,O
simple,O
.,O
you,O
just,O
can,O
’,O
t,O
have,O
more,O
votes,O
than,O
people,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
more,O
votes,O
than,O
people,O
",",O
and,O
that,O
is,O
the,O
least,O
of,O
it,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
flip,O
michigan,LOC_B
back,O
to,O
trump,PER_B
.,O
detroit,LOC_B
",",O
not,O
surprisingly,O
",",O
has,O
tremendous,O
problems,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
car,PER_B
##ney,PER_I
:,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
‘,O
s,O
energy,O
plan,O
would,O
evi,O
##sc,O
##erate,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
sand,O
miner,O
##s,O
via,O
@,O
bre,PER_B
##it,PER_I
##bar,PER_I
##tn,PER_I
##ew,PER_I
##s,PER_I
wisconsin, LOC_B
would,O
be,O
bad,O
##ly,O
hurt,O
because,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
would,O
definitely,O
end,O
frac,O
##king,O
.,O
no,O
more,O
sand,O
mine,O
usage,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-11,O
so,O
now,O
the,O
radical,O
left,O
dem,O
##s,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
talk,O
about,O
coll,O
##usion,O
anymore,O
",",O
because,O
the,O
mueller,O
report,O
said,O
there,O
was,O
no,O
coll,O
##usion,O
",",O
they,O
only,O
want,O
to,O
talk,O
about,O
obstruct,O
##ion,O
",",O
even,O
though,O
there,O
was,O
no,O
obstruct,O
##ion,O
or,O
no,O
crime,O
-,O
except,O
for,O
the,O
crime,O
##s,O
committed,O
by,O
the,O
other,O
side,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-07-05,O
happy,O
birth,O
##day,O
to,O
our,O
great,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
@,O
secrets,ORG_B
##ervice,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-01-17,O
so,O
fun,O
##ny,O
to,O
watch,O
schu,PER_B
##mer,PER_I
grove,O
##ling,O
.,O
he,O
called,O
for,O
the,O
fir,O
##ing,O
of,O
bad,O
cop,O
james,PER_B
come,PER_I
##y,PER_I
many,O
times,O
-,O
until,O
i,O
fired,O
him,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-10,O
matthew,PER_B
g,PER_I
.,0
whit,PER_I
##ake,PER_I
##r,PER_I
is,O
a,O
highly,O
respected,O
former,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
attorney,O
from,O
iowa,LOC_B
.,O
he,O
was,O
chosen,O
by,O
jeff,PER_B
sessions,O
to,O
be,O
his,O
chief,ORG_B
of,ORG_I
staff,ORG_I
.,O
i,O
did,O
not,O
know,O
mr,PER_B
.,PER_I
whit,PER_I
##ake,PER_I
##r,PER_I
.,O
likewise,O
",",O
as,O
chief,O
",",O
i,O
did,O
not,O
know,O
mr,PER_B
.,PER_I
whit,PER_I
##ake,PER_I
##r,PER_I
except,O
primarily,O
as,O
he,O
travele,O
##d,O
with,O
a,O
.,O
g,O
.,O
sessions,O
.,O
no,O
social,O
contact,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-12,O
“,O
pel,PER_B
##osi,PER_I
has,O
made,O
a,O
moc,O
##ker,O
##y,O
of,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
.,O
her,O
articles,O
are,O
so,O
weak,O
.,O
but,O
more,O
importantly,O
",",O
she,O
thought,O
she,O
could,O
ex,O
##tor,O
##t,O
the,O
senate,ORG_B
.,O
she,O
could,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
gregg,PER_B
##ja,PER_I
##rre,PER_I
##tt,PER_I
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##and,O
##frie,O
##nds,O
the,O
do,O
nothing,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
are,O
really,O
run,O
by,O
the,O
radical,O
left,O
.,O
too,O
bad,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-03-22,O
will,O
be,O
having,O
a,O
news,O
conference,O
from,O
our,O
beaut,O
##if,O
##ul,O
white,O
house,O
at,O
5,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
many,O
things,O
to,O
discuss,O
.,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-03,O
indiana,LOC_B
rally,O
",",O
and,O
coach,O
bob,PER_B
##by,PER_I
knight,PER_I
",",O
were,O
incredible,O
last,O
night,O
.,O
pack,O
##ed,O
house,O
in,O
honor,O
of,O
mike,PER_B
bra,PER_I
##un,PER_I
for,O
senate,ORG_B
.,O
mike,PER_B
will,O
be,O
a,O
great,O
sen,O
##ator,O
.,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
forget,O
to,O
vote,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-07-11,O
bring,O
back,O
steel,O
##e,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-12,O
.,O
@,O
wes,PER_B
##ley,PER_I
##hu,PER_I
##nt,PER_I
##tx,PER_I
is,O
running,O
for,O
congress,O
in,O
the,O
great,O
state,O
of,O
texas,LOC_B
.,O
he,O
will,O
help,O
us,O
accomplish,O
our,O
america,LOC_B
first,O
policies,O
.,O
wes,PER_B
##ley,PER_I
is,O
strong,O
on,O
crime,O
",",O
the,O
border,O
",",O
our,O
2nd,O
amendment,O
",",O
trade,O
",",O
military,O
and,O
vet,O
##s,O
.,O
wes,PER_B
##ley,PER_I
has,O
my,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-09,O
the,O
so,O
-,O
called,O
whistle,O
##blow,O
##er,O
",",O
before,O
knowing,O
i,O
was,O
going,O
to,O
release,O
the,O
exact,O
transcript,O
",",O
stated,O
that,O
my,O
call,O
with,O
the,O
uk,O
##rain,PER_B
##ian,PER_I
president,PER_I
was,O
“,O
cra,O
##zy,O
",",O
fri,O
##ght,O
##ening,O
",",O
and,O
completely,O
lack,O
##ing,O
in,O
substance,O
related,O
to,O
national,O
security,O
.,O
”,O
this,O
is,O
a,O
very,O
big,O
lie,O
.,O
read,O
the,O
transcript,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-24,O
up,O
big,O
in,O
south,LOC_B
carolina,LOC_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-15,O
open,O
enrollment,O
starts,O
today,O
on,O
lower,O
-,O
priced,O
medicare,O
advantage,O
plans,O
so,O
love,O
##d,O
by,O
our,O
great,O
seniors,O
.,O
cra,O
##zy,O
bern,PER_B
##ie,PER_I
and,O
his,O
band,O
of,O
congressional,O
dem,ORG_B
##s,ORG_I
will,O
out,O
##la,O
##w,O
these,O
plans,O
.,O
disaster,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-05-22,O
3,O
years,O
ago,O
",",O
after,O
jeff,PER_B
sessions,0
rec,O
##use,O
##d,O
him,O
##self,O
",",O
the,O
fraudulent,O
mueller,O
sca,O
##m,O
began,O
.,O
alabama,LOC_B
",",O
do,O
not,O
trust,O
jeff,LOC_B
sessions,O
.,O
he,O
let,O
our,O
country,LOC_B
down,O
.,O
that,O
’,O
s,O
why,O
i,O
endorsed,O
coach,O
tommy,PER_B
tube,PER_I
##rvi,PER_I
##lle,PER_I
(,O
@,O
tt,PER_B
##uber,PER_I
##ville,PER_I
),O
",",O
the,O
true,O
support,O
##er,O
of,O
our,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
agenda,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-07,O
all,O
russia,LOC_B
ho,O
##ax,O
scand,O
##al,O
information,O
was,O
decl,O
##assi,O
##fied,O
by,O
me,O
long,O
ago,O
.,O
unfortunately,O
for,O
our,O
country,O
",",O
people,O
have,O
acted,O
very,O
slowly,O
",",O
especially,O
since,O
it,O
is,O
perhaps,O
the,O
biggest,O
political,O
crime,O
in,O
the,O
history,O
of,O
our,O
country,LOC_B
.,O
act,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-25,O
clint,ORG_B
##on,ORG_I
foundation,ORG_I
donation,O
##s,O
drop,O
42,O
%,O
-,O
which,O
shows,O
that,O
they,O
illegal,O
##ly,O
played,O
the,O
power,O
game,O
.,O
they,O
monetize,O
##d,O
their,O
political,O
influence,O
through,O
the,O
foundation,ORG_B
.,O
“,O
during,O
her,O
tenure,O
the,O
state,O
department,O
was,O
put,O
in,O
the,O
service,O
of,O
the,O
clint,ORG_B
##on,ORG_I
foundation,ORG_I
.,O
”,O
andrew,PER_B
mccarthy,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-12,O
november,O
3rd,O
.,O
will,O
be,O
the,O
most,O
exciting,O
day,O
in,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
election,O
history,O
",",O
even,O
more,O
so,O
than,O
2016,O
.,O
tremendous,O
excitement,O
and,O
enthusiasm,O
",",O
like,O
perhaps,O
never,O
seen,O
before,O
.,O
nobody,O
showing,O
up,O
to,O
sleep,O
##y,O
joe,PER_B
ral,O
##lie,O
##s,O
.,O
places,O
are,O
dead,O
.,O
stif,O
##f,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
see,O
you,O
in,O
florida,LOC_B
ton,O
##ight,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-27,O
death,O
rate,O
of,O
people,O
going,O
into,O
hospitals,O
is,O
much,O
lower,O
now,O
than,O
it,O
was,O
.,O
@,O
msn,ORG_B
##bc,ORG_I
wo,O
##w,O
",",O
msd,ORG_B
##nc,ORG_I
has,O
come,O
a,O
long,O
way,O
!,O
the,O
fact,O
is,O
that,O
we,O
have,O
learned,O
and,O
done,O
a,O
lot,O
about,O
this,O
virus,O
.,O
much,O
different,O
now,O
than,O
when,O
it,O
first,O
arrived,O
on,O
our,O
shore,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
the,O
world,O
’,O
s,O
",",O
from,O
china,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-24,O
carlos,PER_B
will,O
win,O
big,O
",",O
very,O
exciting,O
.,O
great,O
for,O
florida,LOC_B
",",O
great,O
for,O
usa,LOC_B
!,O
he,O
has,O
my,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-10,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
is,O
at,O
it,O
again,O
!,O
they,O
will,O
take,O
any,O
statement,O
from,O
me,O
",",O
no,O
matter,O
how,O
proper,O
or,O
well,O
delivered,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
systematically,O
",",O
in,O
complete,O
conjunction,O
with,O
all,O
of,O
their,O
all,O
##ies,O
",",O
disma,O
##ntl,O
##e,O
it,O
.,O
with,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
",",O
they,O
only,O
give,O
him,O
soft,O
##ball,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
let,O
him,O
read,O
the,O
answers,O
from,O
a,O
telep,O
##rom,O
##pte,O
##r,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-03-09,O
look,O
forward,O
to,O
being,O
in,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
tomorrow,O
in,O
support,O
of,O
rick,PER_B
@,O
sac,PER_B
##con,PER_I
##e,PER_I
##4,PER_I
##pa,PER_I
##18,PER_I
.,O
big,O
crowd,O
expected,O
in,O
moo,O
##n,O
towns,O
##hip,O
.,O
vote,O
rick,PER_B
and,O
see,O
you,O
there,O
!,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-19,O
.,O
@,0
marsh,PER_B
##abl,PER_I
##ack,PER_I
##burn,PER_I
is,O
a,O
wonderful,O
wo,O
##man,O
who,O
has,O
always,O
been,O
there,O
when,O
we,O
have,O
needed,O
her,O
.,O
great,O
on,O
the,O
military,O
",",O
border,O
security,O
and,O
crime,O
.,O
love,O
##s,O
and,O
works,O
hard,O
for,O
the,O
people,O
of,O
tennessee,LOC_B
.,O
she,O
has,O
my,O
full,O
endorsement,O
and,O
i,O
will,O
be,O
there,O
to,O
campaign,O
with,O
her,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-03-14,O
biggest,O
stock,O
market,O
rise,O
in,O
history,O
yesterday,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-08-09,O
space,O
force,O
all,O
the,O
way,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-02,O
mexico,LOC_B
is,O
making,O
a,O
fortune,O
on,O
naf,O
##ta,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
they,O
have,O
very,O
strong,O
border,O
laws,O
-,O
ours,O
are,O
path,O
##etic,O
.,O
with,O
all,O
of,O
the,O
money,O
they,O
make,O
from,O
the,O
u,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
",",O
hopefully,O
they,O
will,O
stop,O
people,O
from,O
coming,O
through,O
their,O
country,O
and,O
into,O
ours,O
",",O
at,O
least,O
until,O
congress,ORG_B
changes,O
our,O
immigration,O
laws,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-03,O
mexico,LOC_B
",",O
canada,LOC_B
and,O
the,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
are,O
a,O
great,O
partnership,O
and,O
will,O
be,O
a,O
very,O
formidable,O
trading,O
force,O
.,O
we,O
will,O
now,O
",",O
because,O
of,O
the,O
us,O
##mc,O
##a,O
",",O
work,O
very,O
well,O
together,O
.,O
great,O
spirit,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-04,O
the,O
truth,O
is,O
that,O
we,O
have,O
a,O
nation,O
that,O
is,O
disg,O
##ust,O
##ed,O
with,O
the,O
fb,ORG_B
##i,ORG_I
.,O
we,O
have,O
a,O
crisis,O
of,O
confidence,O
in,O
the,O
number,O
one,O
law,O
enforcement,O
agency,O
in,O
this,O
country,O
(,O
thanks,O
come,PER_B
##y,PER_I
!,O
),O
.,O
@,O
lou,PER_B
##do,PER_I
##bb,PER_I
##s,PER_I
“,O
it,O
’,O
s,O
a,O
scand,O
##al,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
alan,PER_B
##ders,PER_I
##h,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2017-02-25,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
media,O
knowingly,O
does,O
##n,O
',O
t,O
tell,O
the,O
truth,O
.,O
a,O
great,O
dang,O
##er,O
to,O
our,O
country,LOC_B
.,O
the,O
failing,O
@,O
ny,ORG_B
##times,ORG_I
has,O
become,O
a,O
jo,O
##ke,O
.,O
likewise,O
@,0
cn,ORG_B
##n,ORG_I
.,O
sad,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-08-25,O
big,O
story,O
out,O
that,O
the,O
fb,ORG_B
##i,ORG_I
ignore,O
##d,O
tens,O
of,O
thousands,O
of,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
email,O
##s,O
",",O
many,O
of,O
which,O
are,O
really,O
bad,O
.,O
also,O
gave,O
false,O
election,O
info,O
.,O
i,O
feel,O
sure,O
that,O
we,O
will,O
soon,O
be,O
getting,O
to,O
the,O
bottom,O
of,O
all,O
of,O
this,O
corruption,O
.,O
at,O
some,O
point,O
i,O
may,O
have,O
to,O
get,O
involved,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-04,O
rt,O
@,O
ans,PER_B
##hu,PER_I
##lb,PER_I
##lp,PER_I
##199,PER_I
##6,PER_I
:,O
@,O
real,PER_B
##don,PER_I
##ald,PER_I
##tru,PER_I
##mp,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-07,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
unb,O
##eliev,O
##ably,O
lucky,O
to,O
have,O
him,O
and,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
just,O
awe,O
##d,O
at,O
how,O
well,O
they,O
’,O
ve,O
done,O
.,O
it,O
’,O
s,O
all,O
the,O
trump,PER_B
magic,O
-,O
trump,PER_B
is,O
the,O
magic,O
man,O
.,O
incredible,O
",",O
he,O
’,O
s,O
got,O
the,O
entire,O
media,O
against,O
him,O
",",O
attack,O
##ing,O
him,O
every,O
day,O
",",O
and,O
he,O
pull,O
##s,O
out,O
these,O
enormous,O
wins,O
.,O
”,O
ben,O
stein,O
",",O
“,O
the,O
capitali,O
##st,O
code,O
”,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-10,O
totally,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-18,O
.,O
@,O
stated,ORG_B
##ept,ORG_I
@,O
sec,PER_B
##po,PER_I
##mpe,PER_I
##o,PER_I
outside,O
of,O
the,O
west,O
wing,O
after,O
our,O
meeting,O
this,O
morning,O
in,O
the,O
ova,O
##l,O
office,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-30,O
congress,ORG_B
##wo,O
##man,O
@,O
cath,PER_B
##ym,PER_I
##cm,PER_I
##or,PER_I
##ris,PER_I
of,O
washington,LOC_B
state,LOC_I
is,O
an,O
incredible,O
leader,O
who,O
is,O
respected,O
by,O
everyone,O
in,O
congress,ORG_B
.,O
we,O
need,O
her,O
bad,O
##ly,O
in,O
d,O
.,O
c,O
.,O
to,O
keep,O
building,O
on,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
.,O
she,O
has,O
my,O
strong,O
endorsement,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-09-01,O
“,O
i,O
think,O
today,O
what,O
has,O
happened,O
is,O
that,O
news,O
reporting,O
has,O
become,O
part,O
of,O
the,O
adve,O
##rsa,O
##ry,O
system,O
.,O
”,O
alan,PER_B
der,PER_I
##sho,PER_I
##witz,PER_I
it,O
has,O
become,O
tai,O
##nted,O
and,O
corrupt,O
!,O
dj,O
##t,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-31,O
our,O
military,O
is,O
being,O
mobili,O
##zed,O
at,O
the,O
southern,LOC_B
border,LOC_I
.,O
many,O
more,O
tro,O
##ops,O
coming,O
.,O
we,O
will,O
not,O
let,O
these,O
car,O
##ava,O
##ns,O
",",O
which,O
are,O
also,O
made,O
up,O
of,O
some,O
very,O
bad,O
thu,O
##gs,O
and,O
gan,O
##g,O
members,O
",",O
into,O
the,O
u,LOC_B
.,LOC_I
s,LOC_I
.,LOC_I
our,O
border,O
is,O
sac,O
##red,O
",",O
must,O
come,O
in,O
legally,O
.,O
turn,O
around,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-05-22,O
congress,PER_B
##man,PER_I
mike,PER_I
kelly,PER_I
(,O
@,0
mike,PER_B
##kel,PER_I
##ly,PER_I
##for,PER_I
##pa,PER_I
),O
is,O
an,O
incredible,O
advocate,O
for,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
!,O
he,O
fight,O
##s,O
to,O
lower,O
your,O
taxes,O
",",O
create,O
jobs,O
",",O
protect,O
our,O
borders,O
",",O
and,O
defend,O
the,O
second,O
amendment,O
.,O
mike,PER_B
has,O
my,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
!,O
#,O
pa,O
##16,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-10-11,O
thank,O
you,O
eri,PER_B
##e,PER_I
",",O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
!,O
remember,O
to,O
get,O
out,O
and,O
vote,O
!,O
#,O
[UNK],0
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-01,O
rt,O
@,O
jc,PER_B
##ry,PER_I
##pto,PER_I
##see,PER_I
##d,PER_I
:,O
@,O
db,PER_B
##ong,PER_I
##ino,PER_I
never,PER_I
supporting,PER_I
a,O
fire,O
##man,O
',O
s,O
ball,O
again,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-01,O
oh,O
no,O
",",O
bet,O
##o,O
just,O
dropped,O
out,O
of,O
race,O
for,O
president,O
despite,O
him,O
saying,O
he,O
was,O
“,O
born,O
for,O
this,O
.,O
”,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
think,O
so,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-15,O
tax,O
filings,O
reveal,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
cancer,O
charit,O
##y,O
spent,O
millions,O
on,O
salaries,O
",",O
zero,O
on,O
research,O
via,O
@,O
ny,ORG_B
##post,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2018-12-11,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
has,O
it,O
purpose,O
##ly,O
wrong,O
.,O
many,O
",",O
over,O
ten,O
",",O
are,O
vy,O
##ing,O
for,O
and,O
wanting,O
the,O
white,LOC_B
house,LOC_I
chief,O
of,O
staff,O
position,O
.,O
why,O
would,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
someone,O
want,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
truly,O
great,O
and,O
meaningful,O
jobs,O
in,O
washington,LOC_B
.,O
please,O
report,O
news,O
correctly,O
.,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-23,O
our,O
great,O
rally,O
ton,O
##ight,O
in,O
pennsylvania,LOC_B
.,O
tremendous,O
energy,O
!,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-08-01,O
peg,PER_B
##gy,PER_I
noo,PER_I
##nan,PER_I
",",O
a,O
“,O
conc,O
##ast,O
”,O
msd,ORG_B
##nc,ORG_I
@,O
ws,ORG_B
##j,ORG_I
pu,O
##ppe,O
##t,O
",",O
does,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
have,O
a,O
clu,O
##e,O
",",O
and,O
has,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
for,O
many,O
years,O
.,O
never,O
got,O
the,O
“,O
trump,PER_B
thing,O
”,O
.,O
she,O
plays,O
right,O
into,O
the,O
hands,O
of,O
the,O
stu,O
##pid,O
people,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-04-03,O
the,O
pay,O
##che,O
##ck,O
protection,O
program,O
is,O
now,O
available,O
!,O
#,O
care,O
##sa,O
##ct,O
small,O
business,O
guidance,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
loan,O
resources,O
:,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-01-12,O
sad,O
##ly,O
",",O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
want,O
to,O
stop,O
paying,O
our,O
tro,O
##ops,O
and,O
government,ORG_B
workers,O
in,O
order,O
to,O
give,O
a,O
sweet,O
##hea,O
##rt,O
deal,O
",",O
not,O
a,O
fair,O
deal,O
",",O
for,O
dac,O
##a,O
.,O
take,O
care,O
of,O
our,O
military,O
",",O
and,O
our,O
country,O
",",O
first,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-12,O
congratulations,O
!,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-04,O
big,O
rally,O
in,O
kentucky,LOC_B
ton,O
##ight,O
for,O
a,O
man,O
who,O
has,O
worked,O
really,O
hard,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
done,O
a,O
great,O
job,O
",",O
gov,O
@,O
matt,PER_B
##be,PER_I
##vin,PER_I_I
.,O
kentucky,LOC_B
is,O
having,O
the,O
best,O
economic,O
year,O
ever,O
under,O
matt,PER_B
’,O
s,O
leadership,O
.,O
he,O
is,O
a,O
fantastic,O
guy,O
who,O
love,O
##s,O
our,O
military,O
",",O
our,O
vet,O
##s,O
and,O
our,O
2a,O
.,O
vote,O
tuesday,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-09-03,O
i,O
see,O
that,O
john,PER_B
kerry,PER_I
",",O
the,O
fat,O
##her,O
of,O
the,O
now,O
terminated,O
iran,LOC_B
deal,O
",",O
is,O
thinking,O
of,O
running,O
for,O
president,0
.,O
i,O
should,O
only,O
be,O
so,O
lucky,O
-,O
although,O
the,O
field,O
that,O
is,O
currently,O
asse,O
##mbl,O
##ing,O
looks,O
really,O
good,O
-,O
for,O
me,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-29,O
his,O
lies,O
were,O
made,O
in,O
perhaps,O
the,O
most,O
bla,O
##tant,O
and,O
sin,O
##ister,O
manner,O
ever,O
seen,O
in,O
the,O
great,O
chamber,O
.,O
he,O
wrote,O
down,O
and,O
read,O
terribl,O
##e,O
things,O
",",O
then,O
said,O
it,O
was,O
from,O
the,O
mouth,O
of,O
the,O
president,O
of,O
the,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
.,O
i,O
want,O
schi,O
##ff,O
questione,O
##d,O
at,O
the,O
highest,O
level,O
for,O
fraud,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
trea,O
##son,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-06-19,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
#,O
[UNK],O
,O
,O
date: 2017-07-29,O
"""",O
i,O
love,O
reading,O
about,O
all,O
of,O
the,O
"""",O
"""",O
geni,O
##use,O
##s,O
"""",O
"""",O
who,O
were,O
so,O
instrumental,O
in,O
my,O
election,O
success,O
.,O
problem,O
is,O
",",O
most,O
don,O
',O
t,O
exist,O
.,O
#,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
!,O
mag,O
##a,O
"""",O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-30,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
election,O
",",O
and,O
neg,O
##ate,O
the,O
votes,O
of,O
millions,O
of,O
evan,O
##gel,O
##ical,O
##s,O
in,O
the,O
process,O
.,O
they,O
know,O
the,O
only,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##able,O
offens,O
##e,O
that,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
has,O
committed,O
was,O
beating,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
clint,PER_I
##on,PER_I
in,O
2016,O
.,O
that,O
’,O
s,O
the,O
unpa,O
##rd,O
##ona,O
##ble,O
sin,O
for,O
which,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
will,O
never,O
forgive,O
him,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-01-04,O
thank,O
you,O
to,O
ford,O
for,O
scrapp,O
##ing,O
a,O
new,O
plant,O
in,O
mexico,LOC_B
and,O
creating,O
700,O
new,O
jobs,O
in,O
the,O
u,LOC_B
.,LOC_I
s,LOC_I
.,LOC_I
this,O
is,O
just,O
the,O
beginning,O
-,O
much,O
more,O
to,O
follow,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-06-09,O
relief,O
is,O
on,O
the,O
way,O
to,O
utah,LOC_B
!,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
proud,O
to,O
send,O
$,O
187,O
.,O
18,O
##m,O
in,O
care,O
##s,O
act,O
funding,O
to,O
@,O
ride,O
##uta,O
.,O
this,O
money,O
will,O
keep,O
people,O
moving,O
and,O
support,O
a,O
swift,O
and,O
smooth,O
economic,O
recovery,O
for,O
the,O
great,O
people,O
of,O
utah,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-22,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-09-26,O
but,O
while,O
dallas,ORG_B
dropped,O
to,O
its,O
knees,O
as,O
a,O
team,O
",",O
they,O
all,O
stood,O
up,O
for,O
our,O
national,O
anthem,O
.,O
big,O
progress,O
being,O
made,O
-,O
we,O
all,O
love,O
our,O
country,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-15,O
incredible,O
young,O
",",O
strong,O
and,O
bri,O
##lli,O
##ant,O
people,O
.,O
army,O
/,O
navy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-23,O
when,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
in,O
congress,O
refi,O
##nish,O
",",O
for,O
the,O
5th,O
time,O
",",O
their,O
fa,O
##ke,O
work,O
on,O
their,O
very,O
disappointing,O
mueller,PER_B
report,O
finding,O
",",O
they,O
will,O
have,O
the,O
time,O
to,O
get,O
the,O
real,O
work,O
of,O
the,O
people,O
done,O
.,O
move,O
quickly,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-17,O
tell,O
jennifer,PER_B
williams,PER_I
",",O
who,O
##ever,O
that,O
is,O
",",O
to,O
read,O
both,O
transcript,O
##s,O
of,O
the,O
presidential,O
calls,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
see,O
the,O
just,O
released,O
st,O
##ste,O
##ment,O
from,O
ukraine,ORG_B
.,O
then,O
she,O
should,O
meet,O
with,O
the,O
other,O
never,O
trump,PER_B
##ers,PER_I
",",O
who,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
know,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
mostly,O
never,O
even,O
heard,O
of,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
work,O
out,O
a,O
better,O
presidential,O
attack,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-29,O
correct,O
",",O
a,O
total,O
sca,O
##m,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-30,O
headline,O
:,O
“,O
kim,O
prepared,O
to,O
cede,O
nuclear,O
weapons,O
if,O
u,ORG_B
.,ORG_I
s,ORG_I
.,ORG_I
pledge,O
##s,O
not,O
to,O
inva,O
##de,O
”,O
-,O
from,O
the,O
failing,O
new,ORG_B
york,ORG_I
times,ORG_I
.,O
also,O
",",O
will,O
shut,O
down,O
nuclear,O
test,O
site,O
in,O
may,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-16,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
work,O
that,O
way,O
.,O
i,O
have,O
a,O
better,O
idea,O
.,O
look,O
at,O
the,O
obama,PER_B
book,O
deal,O
",",O
or,O
the,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
netflix,ORG_B
deal,O
.,O
then,O
look,O
at,O
all,O
the,O
deals,O
made,O
by,O
the,O
dem,ORG_B
##s,ORG_I
in,O
congress,O
",",O
the,O
“,O
congressional,O
slu,O
##sh,O
fund,O
",",O
”,O
and,O
lastly,O
the,O
ig,O
reports,O
.,O
take,O
a,O
look,O
at,O
them,O
.,O
those,O
investigations,O
would,O
be,O
over,O
fast,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-21,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
wo,O
##w,O
",",O
he,O
just,O
voted,O
against,O
me,O
in,O
a,O
big,O
court,O
decision,O
on,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
(,O
of,O
which,O
there,O
was,O
much,O
!,O
),O
",",O
despite,O
many,O
pages,O
of,O
diss,O
##ent,O
from,O
three,O
highly,O
respected,O
justice,O
##s,O
.,O
one,O
thing,O
has,O
nothing,O
to,O
do,O
with,O
another,O
",",O
but,O
we,O
ended,O
up,O
losing,O
4,O
-,O
3,O
in,O
a,O
really,O
incorrect,O
ruling,O
!,O
great,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-18,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
is,O
open,O
for,O
business,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-18,O
the,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
dn,O
##c,O
is,O
working,O
overtime,O
to,O
take,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##t,ORG_I
nom,O
##ination,O
away,O
from,O
bern,PER_B
##ie,PER_I
",",O
again,O
!,O
watch,O
what,O
happens,O
to,O
the,O
super,O
delegate,O
##s,O
in,O
round,O
two,O
.,O
a,O
rig,O
##ged,O
convention,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-01-19,O
great,O
concert,O
at,O
4,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
today,O
at,O
lincoln,O
memorial,O
.,O
enjoy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-12,O
big,O
show,O
ton,O
##ight,O
on,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
!,O
9,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
on,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-08-15,O
thank,O
you,O
to,O
the,O
great,O
pat,PER_B
lynch,PER_I
&,O
amp,O
;,O
the,O
@,O
nyc,PER_B
##p,PER_I
##ba,PER_I
.,O
i,O
will,O
never,O
let,O
you,O
down,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-04-14,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
must,O
change,O
the,O
immigration,O
laws,O
fast,O
.,O
if,O
not,O
",",O
san,O
##ct,O
##uary,O
cities,O
must,O
immediately,O
act,O
to,O
take,O
care,O
of,O
the,O
illegal,O
imm,O
##ig,O
##rant,O
##s,O
-,O
and,O
this,O
includes,O
gan,O
##g,O
members,O
",",O
drug,O
dealers,O
",",O
human,O
traffic,O
##kers,O
",",O
and,O
criminal,O
##s,O
of,O
all,O
shape,O
##s,O
",",O
sizes,O
and,O
kinds,O
.,O
change,O
the,O
laws,O
now,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-12,O
“,O
justice,O
##s,O
ali,PER_B
##to,PER_I
and,O
thomas,PER_B
say,O
they,O
would,O
have,O
allowed,O
texas,ORG_B
to,O
proceed,O
with,O
its,O
election,O
lawsuit,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
sean,PER_B 
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
this,O
is,O
a,O
great,O
and,O
disg,O
##rac,O
##ef,O
##ul,O
misc,O
##arri,O
##age,O
of,O
justice,O
.,O
the,O
people,O
of,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
were,O
che,O
##ated,O
",",O
and,O
our,O
country,O
disg,O
##rac,O
##ed,O
.,O
never,O
even,O
given,O
our,O
day,O
in,O
court,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-30,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
they,O
made,O
this,O
whole,O
thing,O
up,O
.,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
is,O
also,O
a,O
pre,O
-,O
emp,O
##tive,O
strike,O
for,O
what,O
they,O
think,O
is,O
coming,O
on,O
the,O
obama,ORG_B
administration,ORG_I
’,O
s,O
handling,O
of,O
the,O
2016,O
election,O
.,O
”,O
jim,PER_B
mcl,PER_I
##aug,PER_I
##hl,PER_I
##in,PER_I
",",O
highly,O
respected,O
poll,O
##ster,O
.,O
@,O
wash,ORG_B
##times,ORG_I
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-15,O
john,PER_B
bolton,PER_I
was,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
dum,O
##bes,O
##t,O
people,O
in,O
government,O
that,O
i,O
’,O
ve,O
had,O
the,O
“,O
pleasure,O
”,O
to,O
work,O
with,O
.,O
a,O
sul,O
##len,O
",",O
dul,O
##l,O
and,O
quiet,O
guy,O
",",O
he,O
added,O
nothing,O
to,O
national,O
security,O
except,O
",",O
“,O
ge,O
##e,O
",",O
let,O
’,O
s,O
go,O
to,O
war,O
.,O
”,O
also,O
",",O
illegal,O
##ly,O
released,O
much,O
classified,O
information,O
.,O
a,O
real,O
do,O
##pe,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-08,O
the,O
wonderful,O
charles,PER_B
pay,O
##ne,O
@,O
cv,PER_B
##pay,PER_I
##ne,PER_I
of,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
just,O
wrote,O
a,O
great,O
and,O
insp,O
##ira,O
##tional,O
new,O
book,O
",",O
uns,O
##top,O
##pa,O
##ble,O
prosper,O
##ity,O
.,O
get,O
it,O
now,O
.,O
so,O
many,O
important,O
thoughts,O
and,O
suggesti,O
##ons,O
on,O
investing,O
and,O
“,O
making,O
money,O
”,O
.,O
also,O
",",O
charles,PER_B
just,O
happens,O
to,O
be,O
a,O
great,O
guy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-07,O
i,O
just,O
hope,O
the,O
vote,O
##r,O
understands,O
that,O
they,O
are,O
all,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
trying,O
hard,O
to,O
push,O
a,O
man,O
that,O
should,O
never,O
be,O
president,O
of,O
our,O
country,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-01,O
will,O
be,O
interview,O
##ed,O
ton,O
##ight,O
by,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
at,O
9,O
:,O
00,O
.,O
enjoy,O
!,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2019-06-22,O
looking,O
good,O
.,O
we,O
must,O
win,O
to,O
keep,O
america,ORG_B
great,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-02-13,O
wonderful,O
meeting,O
with,O
canadian,O
pm,O
@,O
justin,PER_B
##tru,PER_I
##de,PER_I
##au,PER_I
and,O
a,O
group,O
of,O
leading,O
ceo,O
',O
s,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
business,O
women,O
from,O
[UNK],ORG_B
th,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-08-13,O
as,O
usual,O
",",O
china,ORG_B
said,O
they,O
were,O
going,O
to,O
be,O
buying,O
“,O
big,O
”,O
from,O
our,O
great,O
american,O
farmers,O
.,O
so,O
far,O
they,O
have,O
not,O
done,O
what,O
they,O
said,O
.,O
maybe,O
this,O
will,O
be,O
different,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-09-14,O
we,O
love,O
the,O
#,O
ca,PER_B
##jun,PER_I
##nav,PER_I
##y,PER_I
-,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
#,O
flor,PER_B
##ence,PER_I
##hur,PER_I
##rica,PER_I
##ne,PER_I
##201,O
##8,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-01,O
oh,O
’,O
i,O
see,O
!,O
now,O
that,O
the,O
2,O
year,O
russian,O
coll,O
##usion,O
case,O
has,O
fallen,O
apart,O
",",O
there,O
was,O
no,O
coll,O
##usion,O
except,O
bye,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
and,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
",",O
they,O
say,O
",",O
“,O
ge,O
##e,O
",",O
i,O
have,O
an,O
idea,O
",",O
let,O
’,O
s,O
look,O
at,O
trump,PER_B
’,O
s,O
finances,O
and,O
every,O
deal,O
he,O
has,O
ever,O
done,O
.,O
let,O
’,O
s,O
follow,O
discr,O
##edit,O
##ed,O
michael,PER_B
cohen,PER_I
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-02-19,O
the,O
failed,O
fast,O
train,O
project,O
in,O
california,LOC_B
",",O
were,O
the,O
cost,O
overruns,O
are,O
becoming,O
world,O
record,O
setting,O
",",O
is,O
hundreds,O
of,O
times,O
more,O
expensive,O
than,O
the,O
des,O
##perat,O
##ely,O
needed,O
wall,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-11,O
amazing,O
evening,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-16,O
“,O
here,O
in,O
america,LOC_B
it,O
will,O
be,O
the,O
same,O
victory,O
as,O
brexit,O
",",O
but,O
even,O
more,O
so,O
.,O
in,O
the,O
u,ORG_B
.,ORG_I
s,ORG_I
.,ORG_I
",",O
while,O
all,O
of,O
this,O
has,O
been,O
going,O
on,O
",",O
the,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
",",O
the,O
obstruct,O
##ion,O
",",O
the,O
resistance,O
",",O
president,O
trump,PER_B
has,O
managed,O
to,O
deliver,O
not,O
just,O
promises,O
",",O
but,O
a,O
record,O
which,O
adds,O
up,O
to,O
one,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-07,O
in,O
all,O
fairness,O
",",O
nancy,O
pel,O
##osi,O
deserves,O
to,O
be,O
chosen,O
speaker,O
of,O
the,O
house,O
by,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
.,O
if,O
they,O
give,O
her,O
a,O
hard,O
time,O
",",O
perhaps,O
we,O
will,O
add,O
some,O
republic,PER_B
##an,PER_I
votes,O
.,O
she,O
has,O
earned,O
this,O
great,O
honor,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-25,O
“,O
the,O
special,O
counsel,O
did,O
not,O
find,O
that,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
",",O
or,O
anyone,O
associated,O
with,O
it,O
",",O
cons,O
##pired,O
or,O
coordinated,O
with,O
the,O
russian,O
government,O
in,O
these,O
efforts,O
",",O
despite,O
multiple,O
offers,O
from,O
russian,O
-,O
affiliated,O
individuals,O
to,O
assist,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
.,O
”,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-12-24,O
to,O
those,O
few,O
sen,O
##ators,O
who,O
think,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
like,O
or,O
appreciate,O
being,O
allied,O
with,O
other,O
countries,O
",",O
they,O
are,O
wrong,O
",",O
i,O
do,O
.,O
what,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
like,O
",",O
however,O
",",O
is,O
when,O
many,O
of,O
these,O
same,O
countries,O
take,O
advantage,O
of,O
their,O
friends,O
##hip,O
with,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
",",O
both,O
in,O
military,O
protection,O
and,O
trade,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-02,O
soh,PER_B
##rab,PER_I
ah,PER_I
##mari,PER_I
",",O
new,ORG_B
york,ORG_I
post,ORG_I
“,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
raised,O
$,O
10,O
million,O
in,O
the,O
two,O
days,O
following,O
the,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
(,O
sca,O
##m,O
),O
vote,O
.,O
it,O
seems,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
have,O
shot,O
themselves,O
in,O
the,O
foot,O
in,O
one,O
more,O
way,O
.,O
they,O
set,O
up,O
a,O
process,O
they,O
know,O
is,O
not,O
going,O
to,O
lead,O
to,O
the,O
presidents,O
removal,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-06,O
the,O
immigration,O
law,O
institute,O
’,O
s,O
christopher,PER_B
ha,PER_I
##je,PER_I
##c,PER_I
says,O
",",O
“,O
the,O
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
has,O
to,O
look,O
st,O
whether,O
dac,O
##a,O
is,O
law,O
##ful,O
.,O
what,O
they,O
are,O
looking,O
at,O
now,O
is,O
whether,O
trump,PER_B
’,O
s,O
rec,O
##isi,O
##on,O
of,O
dac,O
##a,O
is,O
law,O
##ful,O
.,O
must,O
consider,O
law,O
##ful,O
##ness,O
of,O
dac,O
##a,O
itself,O
.,O
looks,O
very,O
odd,O
that,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
does,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-21,O
pennsylvania,PER_B
-,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
forget,O
to,O
get,O
out,O
and,O
vote,O
today,O
for,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
fred,PER_B
kell,PER_I
##er,PER_I
for,O
congress,O
.,O
fred,O
is,O
strong,O
on,O
crime,O
",",O
second,O
amendment,O
",",O
military,O
",",O
vet,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
healthcare,O
.,O
he,O
has,O
my,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-29,O
“,O
this,O
is,O
a,O
big,O
win,O
for,O
america,ORG_B
",",O
and,O
also,O
for,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
.,O
”,O
@,O
ny,O
##post,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-03-08,O
“,O
presidential,O
proc,O
##lam,O
##ation,O
on,O
adjusting,O
imports,O
of,O
aluminum,O
into,O
the,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
”,O
proc,O
##lam,O
##ation,O
:,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-03-24,O
this,O
is,O
not,O
about,O
the,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
green,O
new,O
deal,O
.,O
it,O
is,O
about,O
putting,O
our,O
great,O
workers,O
and,O
companies,O
back,O
to,O
work,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-07-03,O
i,O
interview,O
##ed,O
4,O
very,O
impressive,O
people,O
yesterday,O
.,O
on,O
monday,O
i,O
will,O
be,O
announcing,O
my,O
decision,O
for,O
justice,O
of,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-15,O
slipp,O
##ery,O
james,PER_B
come,PER_I
##y,PER_I
",",O
a,O
man,O
who,O
always,O
ends,O
up,O
bad,O
##ly,O
and,O
out,O
of,O
wha,O
##ck,O
(,O
he,O
is,O
not,O
smart,O
!,O
),O
",",O
will,O
go,O
down,O
as,O
the,O
worst,O
fb,O
##i,O
director,O
in,O
history,O
",",O
by,O
far,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-09,O
i,O
had,O
nothing,O
to,O
do,O
with,O
the,O
decision,O
of,O
our,O
great,O
@,O
vp,O
mike,PER_B
penc,PER_I
##e,PER_I
to,O
stay,O
overnight,O
at,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
trump,PER_B
owned,O
resorts,O
in,O
do,O
##on,O
##be,O
##g,O
",",O
ireland,LOC_B
.,O
mike,PER_B
’,O
s,O
family,O
has,O
lived,O
in,O
do,O
##on,O
##be,O
##g,O
for,O
many,O
years,O
",",O
and,O
he,O
thought,O
that,O
during,O
his,O
very,O
busy,O
european,O
visit,O
",",O
he,O
would,O
stop,O
and,O
see,O
his,O
family,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-13,O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
our,O
factories,O
",",O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
our,O
jobs,O
",",O
and,O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
those,O
four,O
beaut,O
##if,O
##ul,O
words,O
:,O
made,O
in,O
the,O
usa,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-08,O
for,O
cour,O
##age,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
bri,O
##lli,O
##ance,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-06,O
iran,ORG_B
will,O
never,O
have,O
a,O
nuclear,O
wea,O
##pon,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
there,O
is,O
a,O
nas,O
##ty,O
rumo,O
##r,O
out,O
there,O
that,O
@,O
sen,O
##ator,O
##coll,PER_B
##ins,PER_I
of,O
maine,LOC_B
will,O
not,O
be,O
supporting,O
our,O
great,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
nominee,O
.,O
well,O
",",O
she,O
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
support,O
healthcare,O
or,O
my,O
opening,O
up,O
5000,O
square,O
miles,O
of,O
ocean,O
to,O
maine,LOC_B
",",O
so,O
why,O
should,O
this,O
be,O
any,O
different,O
.,O
not,O
worth,O
the,O
work,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-29,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
can,O
you,O
imagine,O
if,O
the,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_I
stol,O
##e,O
a,O
presidential,O
election,O
from,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
-,O
all,O
hell,O
would,O
break,O
out,O
.,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
leadership,O
only,O
wants,O
the,O
path,O
of,O
least,O
resistance,O
.,O
our,O
leaders,O
(,O
not,O
me,O
",",O
of,O
course,O
!,O
),O
are,O
path,O
##etic,O
.,O
they,O
only,O
know,O
how,O
to,O
lose,O
!,O
p,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
i,O
got,O
many,O
sen,O
##ators,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-07-29,O
"""",O
i,O
love,O
reading,O
about,O
all,O
of,O
the,O
"""",O
"""",O
geni,O
##use,O
##s,O
"""",O
"""",O
who,O
were,O
so,O
instrumental,O
in,O
my,O
election,O
success,O
.,O
problem,O
is,O
",",O
most,O
don,O
',O
t,O
exist,O
.,O
#,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
!,O
mag,O
##a,O
"""",O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-30,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
election,O
",",O
and,O
neg,O
##ate,O
the,O
votes,O
of,O
millions,O
of,O
evan,O
##gel,O
##ical,O
##s,O
in,O
the,O
process,O
.,O
they,O
know,O
the,O
only,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##able,O
offens,O
##e,O
that,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
has,O
committed,O
was,O
beating,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
clint,PER_I
##on,PER_I
in,O
2016,O
.,O
that,O
’,O
s,O
the,O
unpa,O
##rd,O
##ona,O
##ble,O
sin,O
for,O
which,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
will,O
never,O
forgive,O
him,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-01-04,O
thank,O
you,O
to,O
ford,O
for,O
scrapp,O
##ing,O
a,O
new,O
plant,O
in,O
mexico,LOC_B
and,O
creating,O
700,O
new,O
jobs,O
in,O
the,O
u,LOC_B
.,LOC_I
s,LOC_I
.,LOC_I
this,O
is,O
just,O
the,O
beginning,O
-,O
much,O
more,O
to,O
follow,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-06-09,O
relief,O
is,O
on,O
the,O
way,O
to,O
utah,LOC_B
!,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
proud,O
to,O
send,O
$,O
187,O
.,O
18,O
##m,O
in,O
care,O
##s,O
act,O
funding,O
to,O
@,O
ride,O
##uta,O
.,O
this,O
money,O
will,O
keep,O
people,O
moving,O
and,O
support,O
a,O
swift,O
and,O
smooth,O
economic,O
recovery,O
for,O
the,O
great,O
people,O
of,O
utah,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-22,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-09-26,O
but,O
while,O
dallas,ORG_B
dropped,O
to,O
its,O
knees,O
as,O
a,O
team,O
",",O
they,O
all,O
stood,O
up,O
for,O
our,O
national,O
anthem,O
.,O
big,O
progress,O
being,O
made,O
-,O
we,O
all,O
love,O
our,O
country,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-15,O
incredible,O
young,O
",",O
strong,O
and,O
bri,O
##lli,O
##ant,O
people,O
.,O
army,O
/,O
navy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-23,O
when,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
in,O
congress,O
refi,O
##nish,O
",",O
for,O
the,O
5th,O
time,O
",",O
their,O
fa,O
##ke,O
work,O
on,O
their,O
very,O
disappointing,O
mueller,PER_B
report,O
finding,O
",",O
they,O
will,O
have,O
the,O
time,O
to,O
get,O
the,O
real,O
work,O
of,O
the,O
people,O
done,O
.,O
move,O
quickly,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-11-17,O
tell,O
jennifer,PER_B
williams,PER_I
",",O
who,O
##ever,O
that,O
is,O
",",O
to,O
read,O
both,O
transcript,O
##s,O
of,O
the,O
presidential,O
calls,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
see,O
the,O
just,O
released,O
st,O
##ste,O
##ment,O
from,O
ukraine,ORG_B
.,O
then,O
she,O
should,O
meet,O
with,O
the,O
other,O
never,O
trump,PER_B
##ers,PER_I
",",O
who,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
know,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
mostly,O
never,O
even,O
heard,O
of,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
work,O
out,O
a,O
better,O
presidential,O
attack,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-29,O
correct,O
",",O
a,O
total,O
sca,O
##m,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-30,O
headline,O
:,O
“,O
kim,O
prepared,O
to,O
cede,O
nuclear,O
weapons,O
if,O
u,ORG_B
.,ORG_I
s,ORG_I
.,ORG_I
pledge,O
##s,O
not,O
to,O
inva,O
##de,O
”,O
-,O
from,O
the,O
failing,O
new,ORG_B
york,ORG_I
times,ORG_I
.,O
also,O
",",O
will,O
shut,O
down,O
nuclear,O
test,O
site,O
in,O
may,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-16,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
work,O
that,O
way,O
.,O
i,O
have,O
a,O
better,O
idea,O
.,O
look,O
at,O
the,O
obama,PER_B
book,O
deal,O
",",O
or,O
the,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
netflix,ORG_B
deal,O
.,O
then,O
look,O
at,O
all,O
the,O
deals,O
made,O
by,O
the,O
dem,ORG_B
##s,ORG_I
in,O
congress,O
",",O
the,O
“,O
congressional,O
slu,O
##sh,O
fund,O
",",O
”,O
and,O
lastly,O
the,O
ig,O
reports,O
.,O
take,O
a,O
look,O
at,O
them,O
.,O
those,O
investigations,O
would,O
be,O
over,O
fast,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-21,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
wo,O
##w,O
",",O
he,O
just,O
voted,O
against,O
me,O
in,O
a,O
big,O
court,O
decision,O
on,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
(,O
of,O
which,O
there,O
was,O
much,O
!,O
),O
",",O
despite,O
many,O
pages,O
of,O
diss,O
##ent,O
from,O
three,O
highly,O
respected,O
justice,O
##s,O
.,O
one,O
thing,O
has,O
nothing,O
to,O
do,O
with,O
another,O
",",O
but,O
we,O
ended,O
up,O
losing,O
4,O
-,O
3,O
in,O
a,O
really,O
incorrect,O
ruling,O
!,O
great,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-18,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
is,O
open,O
for,O
business,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-18,O
the,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
dn,O
##c,O
is,O
working,O
overtime,O
to,O
take,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##t,ORG_I
nom,O
##ination,O
away,O
from,O
bern,PER_B
##ie,PER_I
",",O
again,O
!,O
watch,O
what,O
happens,O
to,O
the,O
super,O
delegate,O
##s,O
in,O
round,O
two,O
.,O
a,O
rig,O
##ged,O
convention,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-01-19,O
great,O
concert,O
at,O
4,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
today,O
at,O
lincoln,O
memorial,O
.,O
enjoy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-12,O
big,O
show,O
ton,O
##ight,O
on,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
!,O
9,O
:,O
00,O
p,O
.,O
m,O
.,O
on,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-08-15,O
thank,O
you,O
to,O
the,O
great,O
pat,PER_B
lynch,PER_I
&,O
amp,O
;,O
the,O
@,O
nyc,PER_B
##p,PER_I
##ba,PER_I
.,O
i,O
will,O
never,O
let,O
you,O
down,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-04-14,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
must,O
change,O
the,O
immigration,O
laws,O
fast,O
.,O
if,O
not,O
",",O
san,O
##ct,O
##uary,O
cities,O
must,O
immediately,O
act,O
to,O
take,O
care,O
of,O
the,O
illegal,O
imm,O
##ig,O
##rant,O
##s,O
-,O
and,O
this,O
includes,O
gan,O
##g,O
members,O
",",O
drug,O
dealers,O
",",O
human,O
traffic,O
##kers,O
",",O
and,O
criminal,O
##s,O
of,O
all,O
shape,O
##s,O
",",O
sizes,O
and,O
kinds,O
.,O
change,O
the,O
laws,O
now,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-12,O
“,O
justice,O
##s,O
ali,PER_B
##to,PER_I
and,O
thomas,PER_B
say,O
they,O
would,O
have,O
allowed,O
texas,ORG_B
to,O
proceed,O
with,O
its,O
election,O
lawsuit,O
.,O
”,O
@,O
sean,PER_B 
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
this,O
is,O
a,O
great,O
and,O
disg,O
##rac,O
##ef,O
##ul,O
misc,O
##arri,O
##age,O
of,O
justice,O
.,O
the,O
people,O
of,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
were,O
che,O
##ated,O
",",O
and,O
our,O
country,O
disg,O
##rac,O
##ed,O
.,O
never,O
even,O
given,O
our,O
day,O
in,O
court,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-30,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
they,O
made,O
this,O
whole,O
thing,O
up,O
.,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
is,O
also,O
a,O
pre,O
-,O
emp,O
##tive,O
strike,O
for,O
what,O
they,O
think,O
is,O
coming,O
on,O
the,O
obama,ORG_B
administration,ORG_I
’,O
s,O
handling,O
of,O
the,O
2016,O
election,O
.,O
”,O
jim,PER_B
mcl,PER_I
##aug,PER_I
##hl,PER_I
##in,PER_I
",",O
highly,O
respected,O
poll,O
##ster,O
.,O
@,O
wash,ORG_B
##times,ORG_I
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-15,O
john,PER_B
bolton,PER_I
was,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
dum,O
##bes,O
##t,O
people,O
in,O
government,O
that,O
i,O
’,O
ve,O
had,O
the,O
“,O
pleasure,O
”,O
to,O
work,O
with,O
.,O
a,O
sul,O
##len,O
",",O
dul,O
##l,O
and,O
quiet,O
guy,O
",",O
he,O
added,O
nothing,O
to,O
national,O
security,O
except,O
",",O
“,O
ge,O
##e,O
",",O
let,O
’,O
s,O
go,O
to,O
war,O
.,O
”,O
also,O
",",O
illegal,O
##ly,O
released,O
much,O
classified,O
information,O
.,O
a,O
real,O
do,O
##pe,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-08,O
the,O
wonderful,O
charles,PER_B
pay,O
##ne,O
@,O
cv,PER_B
##pay,PER_I
##ne,PER_I
of,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
just,O
wrote,O
a,O
great,O
and,O
insp,O
##ira,O
##tional,O
new,O
book,O
",",O
uns,O
##top,O
##pa,O
##ble,O
prosper,O
##ity,O
.,O
get,O
it,O
now,O
.,O
so,O
many,O
important,O
thoughts,O
and,O
suggesti,O
##ons,O
on,O
investing,O
and,O
“,O
making,O
money,O
”,O
.,O
also,O
",",O
charles,PER_B
just,O
happens,O
to,O
be,O
a,O
great,O
guy,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-07,O
i,O
just,O
hope,O
the,O
vote,O
##r,O
understands,O
that,O
they,O
are,O
all,O
fa,O
##ke,O
news,O
trying,O
hard,O
to,O
push,O
a,O
man,O
that,O
should,O
never,O
be,O
president,O
of,O
our,O
country,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-01,O
will,O
be,O
interview,O
##ed,O
ton,O
##ight,O
by,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##hann,PER_I
##ity,PER_I
at,O
9,O
:,O
00,O
.,O
enjoy,O
!,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
,O
,O
date: 2019-06-22,O
looking,O
good,O
.,O
we,O
must,O
win,O
to,O
keep,O
america,ORG_B
great,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2017-02-13,O
wonderful,O
meeting,O
with,O
canadian,O
pm,O
@,O
justin,PER_B
##tru,PER_I
##de,PER_I
##au,PER_I
and,O
a,O
group,O
of,O
leading,O
ceo,O
',O
s,O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
business,O
women,O
from,O
[UNK],ORG_B
th,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-08-13,O
as,O
usual,O
",",O
china,ORG_B
said,O
they,O
were,O
going,O
to,O
be,O
buying,O
“,O
big,O
”,O
from,O
our,O
great,O
american,O
farmers,O
.,O
so,O
far,O
they,O
have,O
not,O
done,O
what,O
they,O
said,O
.,O
maybe,O
this,O
will,O
be,O
different,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-09-14,O
we,O
love,O
the,O
#,O
ca,PER_B
##jun,PER_I
##nav,PER_I
##y,PER_I
-,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
#,O
flor,PER_B
##ence,PER_I
##hur,PER_I
##rica,PER_I
##ne,PER_I
##201,O
##8,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-01,O
oh,O
’,O
i,O
see,O
!,O
now,O
that,O
the,O
2,O
year,O
russian,O
coll,O
##usion,O
case,O
has,O
fallen,O
apart,O
",",O
there,O
was,O
no,O
coll,O
##usion,O
except,O
bye,O
cro,O
##oke,O
##d,O
hill,PER_B
##ary,PER_I
and,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
",",O
they,O
say,O
",",O
“,O
ge,O
##e,O
",",O
i,O
have,O
an,O
idea,O
",",O
let,O
’,O
s,O
look,O
at,O
trump,PER_B
’,O
s,O
finances,O
and,O
every,O
deal,O
he,O
has,O
ever,O
done,O
.,O
let,O
’,O
s,O
follow,O
discr,O
##edit,O
##ed,O
michael,PER_B
cohen,PER_I
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-02-19,O
the,O
failed,O
fast,O
train,O
project,O
in,O
california,LOC_B
",",O
were,O
the,O
cost,O
overruns,O
are,O
becoming,O
world,O
record,O
setting,O
",",O
is,O
hundreds,O
of,O
times,O
more,O
expensive,O
than,O
the,O
des,O
##perat,O
##ely,O
needed,O
wall,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-11,O
amazing,O
evening,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-12-16,O
“,O
here,O
in,O
america,LOC_B
it,O
will,O
be,O
the,O
same,O
victory,O
as,O
brexit,O
",",O
but,O
even,O
more,O
so,O
.,O
in,O
the,O
u,ORG_B
.,ORG_I
s,ORG_I
.,ORG_I
",",O
while,O
all,O
of,O
this,O
has,O
been,O
going,O
on,O
",",O
the,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
",",O
the,O
obstruct,O
##ion,O
",",O
the,O
resistance,O
",",O
president,O
trump,PER_B
has,O
managed,O
to,O
deliver,O
not,O
just,O
promises,O
",",O
but,O
a,O
record,O
which,O
adds,O
up,O
to,O
one,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-11-07,O
in,O
all,O
fairness,O
",",O
nancy,O
pel,O
##osi,O
deserves,O
to,O
be,O
chosen,O
speaker,O
of,O
the,O
house,O
by,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
.,O
if,O
they,O
give,O
her,O
a,O
hard,O
time,O
",",O
perhaps,O
we,O
will,O
add,O
some,O
republic,PER_B
##an,PER_I
votes,O
.,O
she,O
has,O
earned,O
this,O
great,O
honor,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-03-25,O
“,O
the,O
special,O
counsel,O
did,O
not,O
find,O
that,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
",",O
or,O
anyone,O
associated,O
with,O
it,O
",",O
cons,O
##pired,O
or,O
coordinated,O
with,O
the,O
russian,O
government,O
in,O
these,O
efforts,O
",",O
despite,O
multiple,O
offers,O
from,O
russian,O
-,O
affiliated,O
individuals,O
to,O
assist,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
.,O
”,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-12-24,O
to,O
those,O
few,O
sen,O
##ators,O
who,O
think,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
like,O
or,O
appreciate,O
being,O
allied,O
with,O
other,O
countries,O
",",O
they,O
are,O
wrong,O
",",O
i,O
do,O
.,O
what,O
i,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
like,O
",",O
however,O
",",O
is,O
when,O
many,O
of,O
these,O
same,O
countries,O
take,O
advantage,O
of,O
their,O
friends,O
##hip,O
with,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
",",O
both,O
in,O
military,O
protection,O
and,O
trade,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-02,O
soh,PER_B
##rab,PER_I
ah,PER_I
##mari,PER_I
",",O
new,ORG_B
york,ORG_I
post,ORG_I
“,O
the,O
trump,O
campaign,O
raised,O
$,O
10,O
million,O
in,O
the,O
two,O
days,O
following,O
the,O
impe,O
##ach,O
##ment,O
(,O
sca,O
##m,O
),O
vote,O
.,O
it,O
seems,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
have,O
shot,O
themselves,O
in,O
the,O
foot,O
in,O
one,O
more,O
way,O
.,O
they,O
set,O
up,O
a,O
process,O
they,O
know,O
is,O
not,O
going,O
to,O
lead,O
to,O
the,O
presidents,O
removal,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
",",O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-06,O
the,O
immigration,O
law,O
institute,O
’,O
s,O
christopher,PER_B
ha,PER_I
##je,PER_I
##c,PER_I
says,O
",",O
“,O
the,O
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
has,O
to,O
look,O
st,O
whether,O
dac,O
##a,O
is,O
law,O
##ful,O
.,O
what,O
they,O
are,O
looking,O
at,O
now,O
is,O
whether,O
trump,PER_B
’,O
s,O
rec,O
##isi,O
##on,O
of,O
dac,O
##a,O
is,O
law,O
##ful,O
.,O
must,O
consider,O
law,O
##ful,O
##ness,O
of,O
dac,O
##a,O
itself,O
.,O
looks,O
very,O
odd,O
that,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
does,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-05-21,O
pennsylvania,PER_B
-,O
don,O
’,O
t,O
forget,O
to,O
get,O
out,O
and,O
vote,O
today,O
for,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
fred,PER_B
kell,PER_I
##er,PER_I
for,O
congress,O
.,O
fred,O
is,O
strong,O
on,O
crime,O
",",O
second,O
amendment,O
",",O
military,O
",",O
vet,O
##s,O
",",O
and,O
healthcare,O
.,O
he,O
has,O
my,O
complete,O
and,O
total,O
endorsement,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-10-29,O
“,O
this,O
is,O
a,O
big,O
win,O
for,O
america,ORG_B
",",O
and,O
also,O
for,O
president,O
trump,PER_B
.,O
”,O
@,O
ny,O
##post,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-03-08,O
“,O
presidential,O
proc,O
##lam,O
##ation,O
on,O
adjusting,O
imports,O
of,O
aluminum,O
into,O
the,O
united,LOC_B
states,LOC_I
”,O
proc,O
##lam,O
##ation,O
:,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-03-24,O
this,O
is,O
not,O
about,O
the,O
rid,O
##icul,O
##ous,O
green,O
new,O
deal,O
.,O
it,O
is,O
about,O
putting,O
our,O
great,O
workers,O
and,O
companies,O
back,O
to,O
work,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-07-03,O
i,O
interview,O
##ed,O
4,O
very,O
impressive,O
people,O
yesterday,O
.,O
on,O
monday,O
i,O
will,O
be,O
announcing,O
my,O
decision,O
for,O
justice,O
of,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-15,O
slipp,O
##ery,O
james,PER_B
come,PER_I
##y,PER_I
",",O
a,O
man,O
who,O
always,O
ends,O
up,O
bad,O
##ly,O
and,O
out,O
of,O
wha,O
##ck,O
(,O
he,O
is,O
not,O
smart,O
!,O
),O
",",O
will,O
go,O
down,O
as,O
the,O
worst,O
fb,O
##i,O
director,O
in,O
history,O
",",O
by,O
far,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2019-09-09,O
i,O
had,O
nothing,O
to,O
do,O
with,O
the,O
decision,O
of,O
our,O
great,O
@,O
vp,O
mike,PER_B
penc,PER_I
##e,PER_I
to,O
stay,O
overnight,O
at,O
one,O
of,O
the,O
trump,PER_B
owned,O
resorts,O
in,O
do,O
##on,O
##be,O
##g,O
",",O
ireland,LOC_B
.,O
mike,PER_B
’,O
s,O
family,O
has,O
lived,O
in,O
do,O
##on,O
##be,O
##g,O
for,O
many,O
years,O
",",O
and,O
he,O
thought,O
that,O
during,O
his,O
very,O
busy,O
european,O
visit,O
",",O
he,O
would,O
stop,O
and,O
see,O
his,O
family,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2018-04-13,O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
our,O
factories,O
",",O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
our,O
jobs,O
",",O
and,O
we,O
are,O
bringing,O
back,O
those,O
four,O
beaut,O
##if,O
##ul,O
words,O
:,O
made,O
in,O
the,O
usa,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-08,O
for,O
cour,O
##age,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
bri,O
##lli,O
##ance,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-06,O
iran,ORG_B
will,O
never,O
have,O
a,O
nuclear,O
wea,O
##pon,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
there,O
is,O
a,O
nas,O
##ty,O
rumo,O
##r,O
out,O
there,O
that,O
@,O
sen,O
##ator,O
##coll,PER_B
##ins,PER_I
of,O
maine,LOC_B
will,O
not,O
be,O
supporting,O
our,O
great,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
supreme,ORG_B
court,ORG_I
nominee,O
.,O
well,O
",",O
she,O
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
support,O
healthcare,O
or,O
my,O
opening,O
up,O
5000,O
square,O
miles,O
of,O
ocean,O
to,O
maine,LOC_B
",",O
so,O
why,O
should,O
this,O
be,O
any,O
different,O
.,O
not,O
worth,O
the,O
work,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-12-29,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
can,O
you,O
imagine,O
if,O
the,O
republic,ORG_B
##ans,ORG_I
stol,O
##e,O
a,O
presidential,O
election,O
from,O
the,O
demo,ORG_B
##cra,ORG_I
##ts,ORG_I
-,O
all,O
hell,O
would,O
break,O
out,O
.,O
republic,ORG_B
##an,ORG_I
leadership,O
only,O
wants,O
the,O
path,O
of,O
least,O
resistance,O
.,O
our,O
leaders,O
(,O
not,O
me,O
",",O
of,O
course,O
!,O
),O
are,O
path,O
##etic,O
.,O
they,O
only,O
know,O
how,O
to,O
lose,O
!,O
p,O
.,O
s,O
.,O
i,O
got,O
many,O
sen,O
##ators,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
