tokens,labels
date: 2020-03-03,O
i,O
was,O
thrilled,O
to,O
be,O
back,O
in,O
the,O
great,O
city,O
of,O
charlotte,LOC_B
",",O
north,LOC_B
carolina,LOC_I
with,O
thousands,O
of,O
hard,O
##working,O
american,O
patriot,O
##s,O
who,O
love,O
our,O
country,O
",",O
cher,O
##ish,O
our,O
values,O
",",O
respect,O
our,O
laws,O
",",O
and,O
always,O
put,O
america,ORG_B
first,O
!,O
thank,O
you,O
for,O
a,O
wonderful,O
evening,O
!,O
!,O
#,O
ka,O
##g,O
##202,O
##0,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-09-12,O
the,O
unsolicited,O
mail,O
in,O
ball,O
##ot,O
sca,O
##m,O
is,O
a,O
major,O
threat,O
to,O
our,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##cy,O
",",O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
the,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##ts,O
know,O
it,O
.,O
almost,O
all,O
recent,O
elections,O
using,O
this,O
system,O
",",O
even,O
though,O
much,O
smaller,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
with,O
far,O
fewer,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
to,O
count,O
",",O
have,O
ended,O
up,O
being,O
a,O
disaster,O
.,O
large,O
numbers,O
of,O
missing,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
fraud,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-02-01,O
getting,O
a,O
little,O
exercise,O
this,O
morning,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-01-09,O
thank,O
you,O
eli,PER_B
##se,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
as,O
per,O
your,O
request,O
",",O
joe,PER_B
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-09,O
the,O
threshold,O
identification,O
of,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
is,O
turning,O
out,O
to,O
be,O
even,O
bigger,O
than,O
originally,O
anticipated,O
.,O
a,O
very,O
large,O
number,O
of,O
ball,O
##ot,O
##s,O
are,O
impacted,O
.,O
stay,O
tune,O
##d,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-12,O
“,O
i,O
’,O
m,O
running,O
as,O
a,O
proud,O
demo,O
##cra,O
##t,O
",",O
for,O
the,O
senate,ORG_B
”,O
.,O
sleep,O
##y,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
today,O
.,O
it,O
’,O
s,O
only,O
going,O
to,O
get,O
worse,O
.,O
it,O
is,O
not,O
sustainable,O
for,O
our,O
county,O
-,O
china,ORG_B
will,O
own,O
us,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
huge,O
win,O
today,O
for,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
states,ORG_I
and,O
for,O
peac,O
##e,O
in,O
the,O
world,O
.,O
su,ORG_B
##dan,ORG_I
has,O
agreed,O
to,O
a,O
peac,O
##e,O
and,O
normalization,O
agreement,O
with,O
israel,ORG_B
!,O
with,O
the,O
united,ORG_B
arab,ORG_I
emi,ORG_I
##rates,ORG_I
and,O
bah,O
##rain,O
",",O
that,O
’,O
s,O
three,O
arab,O
countries,O
to,O
have,O
done,O
so,O
in,O
only,O
a,O
matter,O
of,O
weeks,O
.,O
more,O
will,O
follow,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
thank,O
you,O
meg,PER_B
##yn,PER_I
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-23,O
11,O
days,O
!,O
#,O
mag,O
##a,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-09,O
nevada,LOC_B
is,O
turning,O
out,O
to,O
be,O
a,O
ces,O
##spo,O
##ol,O
of,O
fa,O
##ke,O
votes,O
.,O
@,O
msc,O
##hl,O
##app,O
&,O
amp,O
;,O
@,O
adam,PER_B
##la,PER_I
##xa,PER_I
##lt,PER_I
are,O
finding,O
things,O
that,O
",",O
when,O
released,O
",",O
will,O
be,O
absolutely,O
shock,O
##ing,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-09,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
is,O
looking,O
very,O
good,O
.,O
needs,O
a,O
little,O
time,O
stat,O
##utor,O
##ily,O
.,O
will,O
happen,O
soon,O
!,O
@,O
reinc,O
##e,O
@,O
sean,PER_B
##du,PER_I
##ff,PER_I
##yw,PER_I
##i,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
nobody,O
is,O
showing,O
up,O
for,O
obama,PER_B
’,O
s,O
hate,O
lac,O
##ed,O
speech,O
##es,O
.,O
47,O
people,O
!,O
no,O
energy,O
",",O
but,O
still,O
better,O
than,O
joe,PER_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-09,O
pennsylvania,ORG_B
prevented,O
us,O
from,O
watching,O
much,O
of,O
the,O
ball,O
##ot,O
count,O
.,O
unt,O
##hink,O
##able,O
and,O
illegal,O
in,O
this,O
country,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
just,O
lande,O
##d,O
in,O
ohio,LOC_B
.,O
see,O
you,O
in,O
a,O
little,O
while,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-09,O
georgia,LOC_B
will,O
be,O
a,O
big,O
presidential,O
win,O
",",O
as,O
it,O
was,O
the,O
night,O
of,O
the,O
election,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
thank,O
you,O
ohio,ORG_B
!,O
#,O
vote,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-24,O
great,O
to,O
be,O
in,O
ohio,LOC_B
",",O
leaving,O
now,O
for,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
.,O
see,O
you,O
in,O
a,O
little,O
while,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
very,O
good,O
reviews,O
on,O
last,O
night,O
’,O
s,O
@,O
nbc,O
##new,O
##s,O
town,O
hall,O
in,O
miami,LOC_B
.,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
poll,O
##s,O
numbers,O
are,O
looking,O
very,O
strong,O
.,O
big,O
crowd,O
##s,O
",",O
great,O
enthusiasm,O
.,O
massive,O
red,O
wave,O
coming,O
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
lie,O
##d,O
pennsylvania,ORG_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
thank,O
you,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
thank,O
you,O
libe,PER_B
##rta,PER_I
##rian,PER_I
##s,PER_I
.,O
we,O
are,O
getting,O
it,O
all,O
done,O
",",O
and,O
fast,O
!,O
vote,O
trump,PER_B
!,O
!,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-16,O
the,O
process,O
has,O
long,O
begun,O
.,O
happening,O
fast,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
this,O
is,O
good,O
news,O
",",O
it,O
means,O
i,O
won,O
!,O
cc,O
:,O
@,O
rep,PER_B
##do,PER_I
##ug,PER_I
##coll,PER_I
##ins,PER_I
@,O
secretary,PER_B
##son,PER_I
##ny,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
and,O
i,O
won,O
the,O
election,O
.,O
vote,O
##r,O
fraud,O
all,O
over,O
the,O
country,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
dominion,O
is,O
running,O
our,O
election,O
.,O
rig,O
##ged,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
the,O
worst,O
poll,O
##ing,O
ever,O
",",O
and,O
then,O
they,O
’,O
ll,O
be,O
back,O
in,O
four,O
years,O
to,O
do,O
it,O
again,O
.,O
this,O
is,O
much,O
more,O
then,O
vote,O
##r,O
and,O
campaign,O
finance,O
suppressi,O
##on,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
thank,O
you,O
ohio,ORG_B
!,O
#,O
vote,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
what,O
a,O
terribl,O
##e,O
thing,O
for,O
bid,PER_B
##en,PER_I
to,O
say,O
!,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
?,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
i,O
strongly,O
stand,O
with,O
kelly,PER_B
&,O
amp,O
;,O
david,PER_B
.,O
they,O
are,O
both,O
great,O
and,O
must,O
win,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
lande,O
##d,O
in,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
.,O
big,O
crowd,O
.,O
on,O
my,O
way,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
as,O
i,O
have,O
long,O
said,O
",",O
@,O
pfizer,ORG_B
and,O
the,O
others,O
would,O
only,O
announce,O
a,O
vaccine,O
after,O
the,O
election,O
",",O
because,O
they,O
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
have,O
the,O
cour,O
##age,O
to,O
do,O
it,O
before,O
.,O
likewise,O
",",O
the,O
@,O
us,ORG_B
_,O
fda,ORG_B
should,O
have,O
announced,O
it,O
earlier,O
",",O
not,O
for,O
political,O
purposes,O
",",O
but,O
for,O
saving,O
lives,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
abc,O
/,O
wa,O
##po,O
had,O
me,O
down,O
17,O
points,O
in,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
",",O
the,O
day,O
before,O
the,O
election,O
",",O
and,O
i,O
won,O
!,O
in,O
iowa,LOC_B
",",O
the,O
poll,O
##s,O
had,O
us,O
4,O
points,O
down,O
",",O
and,O
i,O
won,O
by,O
8,O
.,O
2,O
%,O
!,O
fox,ORG_B
news,ORG_I
and,O
quinn,ORG_B
##ip,ORG_I
##ia,ORG_I
##c,ORG_I
were,O
wrong,O
on,O
everything,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
.,O
@,O
fox,ORG_B
##new,ORG_I
##s,ORG_I
",",O
@,O
quinn,ORG_B
##ip,ORG_I
##ia,ORG_I
##cp,ORG_I
##oll,ORG_I
",",O
abc,O
/,O
wa,ORG_B
##po,ORG_I
",",O
nbc,O
/,O
ws,ORG_B
##j,ORG_I
were,O
so,O
inaccurate,O
with,O
their,O
poll,O
##s,O
on,O
me,O
",",O
that,O
it,O
really,O
is,O
tamp,O
##ering,O
with,O
an,O
election,O
.,O
they,O
were,O
so,O
far,O
off,O
in,O
their,O
poll,O
##ing,O
",",O
and,O
in,O
their,O
attempt,O
to,O
suppress,O
-,O
that,O
they,O
should,O
be,O
called,O
out,O
for,O
election,O
interference,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
if,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
were,O
president,O
",",O
you,O
would,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
have,O
the,O
vaccine,O
for,O
another,O
four,O
years,O
",",O
nor,O
would,O
the,O
@,O
us,ORG_B
_,O
fda,ORG_B
have,O
ever,O
approved,O
it,O
so,O
quickly,O
.,O
the,O
bureau,O
##cra,O
##cy,O
would,O
have,O
destroye,O
##d,O
millions,O
of,O
lives,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
the,O
@,O
us,ORG_B
_,O
fda,ORG_B
and,O
the,O
demo,PER_B
##cra,PER_I
##ts,PER_I
did,O
##n,O
’,O
t,O
want,O
to,O
have,O
me,O
get,O
a,O
vaccine,O
win,O
",",O
prior,O
to,O
the,O
election,O
",",O
so,O
instead,O
it,O
came,O
out,O
five,O
days,O
later,O
–,O
as,O
i,O
’,O
ve,O
said,O
all,O
along,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
who,O
will,O
be,O
running,O
for,O
governor,O
of,O
the,O
great,O
state,O
of,O
ohio,LOC_B
?,O
will,O
be,O
hot,O
##ly,O
contest,O
##ed,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
another,O
vaccine,O
just,O
announced,O
.,O
this,O
time,O
by,O
modern,ORG_B
##a,ORG_I
",",O
95,O
%,O
effective,O
.,O
for,O
those,O
great,O
“,O
hist,O
##ori,O
##ans,O
”,O
",",O
please,O
remember,O
that,O
these,O
great,O
discoveries,O
",",O
which,O
will,O
end,O
the,O
china,O
plagu,O
##e,O
",",O
all,O
took,O
place,O
on,O
my,O
watch,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-16,O
the,O
fa,O
##ke,O
reco,O
##unt,O
going,O
on,O
in,O
georgia,LOC_B
means,O
nothing,O
because,O
they,O
are,O
not,O
allowing,O
signature,O
##s,O
to,O
be,O
looked,O
at,O
and,O
verified,O
.,O
break,O
the,O
uncon,O
##stitut,O
##ional,O
consent,O
decree,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
flo,PER_B
##yd,PER_I
county,O
",",O
georgia,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
.,O
.,O
.,O
and,O
a,O
great,O
show,O
by,O
@,O
jess,PER_B
##eb,PER_I
##watt,PER_I
##ers,PER_I
ton,O
##ight,O
.,O
watche,O
##d,O
it,O
on,O
way,O
from,O
ohio,LOC_B
to,O
wisconsin,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-18,O
this,O
was,O
a,O
rig,O
##ged,O
election,O
.,O
no,O
republic,O
##an,O
poll,O
watche,O
##rs,O
allowed,O
",",O
voting,O
machine,O
“,O
gli,O
##tche,O
##s,O
”,O
all,O
over,O
the,O
place,O
(,O
meaning,O
they,O
got,O
caught,O
che,O
##ating,O
!,O
),O
",",O
voting,O
after,O
election,O
ended,O
",",O
and,O
so,O
much,O
more,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
law,O
enforcement,O
is,O
watching,O
and,O
involved,O
.,O
so,O
dish,O
##one,O
##st,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
thank,O
you,O
wisconsin,ORG_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
nol,O
##te,O
:,O
bret,PER_B
bai,PER_I
##er,PER_I
delete,O
##s,O
twe,O
##et,O
that,O
exposed,O
back,O
##las,O
##h,O
against,O
fox,ORG_B
news,ORG_I
via,O
@,O
bre,PER_B
##it,PER_I
##bar,PER_I
##tn,PER_I
##ew,PER_I
##s,PER_I
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
this,O
is,O
the,O
most,O
important,O
election,O
in,O
the,O
history,O
of,O
our,O
country,O
.,O
with,O
your,O
vote,O
",",O
we,O
will,O
continue,O
to,O
bring,O
back,O
your,O
jobs,O
",",O
lower,O
drug,O
prices,O
",",O
support,O
our,O
police,O
",",O
protect,O
the,O
#,O
2a,O
",",O
defend,O
our,O
borders,O
",",O
and,O
ensure,O
more,O
products,O
are,O
proud,O
##ly,O
stamp,O
##ed,O
with,O
the,O
ph,O
##rase,O
made,O
in,O
the,O
usa,LOC_B
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-19,O
we,O
withdrew,O
because,O
we,O
won,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-11-10,O
nothing,O
!,O
,O
,O
date: 2020-10-25,O
as,O
long,O
as,O
i,O
am,O
president,O
",",O
i,O
will,O
always,O
stand,O
with,O
the,O
hero,O
##es,O
of,O
law,O
enforcement,O
!,O
joe,PER_B
bid,PER_I
##en,PER_I
won,O
’,O
t,O
.,O
,O
,O
